Harold arnd Kumar
哈樂德 卡瑪
Billy Boy! Get your ass ready.
比利! 快點給我出來
lt's almost 5:00, and this bad boy needs to get his drink on.
差不多5點了, 我們有酒宴
- No, no, no. Give me that. - Don't.
- 不,不行,給我 - 別這樣
- l'm gonna burn it once and for all. - Stop that.
- 我一定要把它燒掉 - 停下
Dude, it's been six months. lt's time to move on, okay?
老兄,已經六個月了 是該換一個了,不是嗎?
Whatever. Even if l wanted to meet other women,
不管怎樣,就算我碰到了其他女人
l wouldn't even know what to do.
我甚至都不知道該怎麼做了
l've been out of the game for so long.
我離開這種遊戲太久了
Dude, you come out with me tonight, l promise you will get laid.
老兄,今晚和我一起出去 我保證你能泡到一個
Yeah, it sounds very tempting,
是啊,聽起來非常誘人
but Berenson needs me to update these financial models
但是貝爾森要我校正這些金融議案
for the meeting with the foreign investors.
準備下次和外國投資者的會議
So what? lt's Friday night.
那又怎樣? 今天是週末
The Germans are taking an early flight back.
德國人提早飛回來了
The meeting got changed to tomorrow.
會議改在明天進行
So? Why don't you just get somebody else
為什麼不叫其他人做?
to do your work for you?
做你的工作?
Who?
叫誰?
Harold, l need you to update those models for me.
哈樂德,我需要你幫忙校正這些議案
- Billy, aren't you supposed to-- - l know. Something just came up.
- 比利,你不是打算自己—— - 我知道,突然有些事情
l have this meeting with these new clients tonight,
今天晚上我和客戶們有個會議
and l'm never gonna have time to get to those.
沒時間幹這些了
So that's your responsibility now, big boy.
現在這些交給你了,好傢伙
Make sure those are in by 9:00 sharp tomorrow.
確保明早九點之前一定要完成
With all the downsizing that's been going on around here,
現在裁員之風盛行
we wouldn't want to have to tell Berenson you've been slacking, now would we?
我們不想告訴貝爾森你行事馬虎,對嗎?
Yeah.
好的
Okay, no problem.
好吧,沒問題
Hey.
嘿
You have a great weekend, okay, buddy?
祝你週末愉快,夥計
l owe you one. Just one.
我欠你一個人情,就一個
Thank you.
謝謝
Wow! That was amazing. l cannot believe how easy that was.
喔!這麼簡單就搞定,真令人驚奇
Dude, how do you think l get all my shit done?
老兄,你覺得我的餿主意怎麼樣
l'm telling you, those Asian guys love crunching numbers.
我跟你說,那些亞洲人喜歡幹這些
You probably just made his weekend.
你或許剛好讓他有個充實的週末
Fuck.
媽的
An excellent point, Mr. Patel.
好極了,派特先生
You are one of the finest applicants l have ever interviewed.
你是我會見過最好的申請者之一
Thank you.
謝謝
lt comes as no surprise. Your father is highly respected in his field.
不奇怪,你父親在他的領域也倍受尊敬
As you probably heard from your old man,
你一定從父親那媗本★L了
he and l had some pretty wild times back in med school.
我和他在學校埵酗@些瘋狂的回憶
Really?
真的嗎?
Yeah. We started our own basketball team--
是的,我們創立了自己的籃球隊－－
the Hemoglobin Trotters.
Hemoglobin Trotters 校隊
Hemo-globin Trotters-- get it?
Hemo-globin Trotters－－ 清楚了嗎?
A play on the name of the famous colored, Negro basketball squad--
我們經常參加著名的黑人籃球賽
black, African-American.
黑人,美籍非裔人
You know, people of colors.
你知道,有色人種
Let's end up with one final question, just as a formality.
最後來一個問題吧,只是形式上的
What are some potential symptoms of pancreatitis?
胰腺炎有哪些潛在的症狀?
Well, you would have epigastric tenderness,
嗯,你的腹上部會比較敏感
diffuse abdominal tenderness...
一直擴散到腹部...
l'm sorry. Can you hold on one second?
抱歉,能等下嗎?
Kumar's phone. Kumar speaking.
喂,我是卡瑪
Hey, what's up? lt's me. What are you doing?
嘿,怎麼樣?是我,你在做什麼?
Nothing important. l can talk. What's going on?
沒什麼重要的事,我能交談, 有什麼事情嗎?
Listen, l can't party tonight, okay? l gotta stay late at the office.
聽著,今晚不能辦派對了,好嗎? 我必須呆在辦公室晚點回去
Dude, fuck that shit. We had plans.
老兄,你他媽的別放狗屁,我們計畫好了
l know, but l got a lot of work to do.
我知道,但我有許多工作要幹
When has getting high ever prevented you from doing your work?
當你陶醉於大麻就不會想到工作了
Jesus!
天啊!
Believe me. l would love to come lhome. okay?
相信我,我會儘快趕回去的,好嗎?
- l got a lot of work to do. - Thank you. l'll do that.
- 我有許多的工作要做 - 謝謝,我自己來
l got a quarter of the finest herb in New York City.
我從紐約帶回了一些最好的大麻
l'm not smoking that shit alone, okay?
我總不能一個人享受,對嗎?
So you need to just chill the fuck out and prepare to get blazed
所以你就別管那些事 做好思想準備
because in the next couple of hours,
因為在接下來的幾個小時,
l expect both of us to be blitzed out of our skulls, got it?
我希望我們一塊兒神遊體外 爽到極點, 你明白麼?
All right, l got it.
好的,我明白了
l'll talk to you later. Where was l?
我等下再和你談 我說到哪兒了?
We've got the severe anal discharge, sometimes violent--a.k.a. diarrhea.
然後會有一些肛門排泄物，有時還 很嚴重--即a.k.a. 腹瀉.
Mr. Patel, l am more than familiar with diarrhea.
派特先生, 我比你更熟悉腹瀉
Do you actually believe after the way you've just behaved
你居然還認為看過你的行為舉止後
that l would ever even consider recommending you for admission?
我還會考慮推薦你入學嗎?
No. l'm gonna be honest with you.
沒有,我只想對你說實話
The only reason l'm applying
我申請的唯一原因
is so my dad will keep paying for my apartment.
是那樣我爸爸會繼續付我的房租
l really don't have a desire to go to med school.
我真的從沒渴望進入哪個醫學院
But you have perfect MCAT scores.
但你醫學院入學考試得了高分
Yeah. Just 'cause you're hung like a moose
是啊，但那就象你那玩意 壯得跟駝鹿似的
doesn't mean you gotta do porn.
也不意味著你要去拍色情片
Get out! Bernadette, show this young man to the door!
出去! 伯納黛特 把這個男人帶出去
And please bring in some fresh diarrhe--dry towels!
還有請拿一些新鮮的腹瀉--乾毛巾進來
Yes!
好的!
Right in front of the door.
剛好能停在門口
This is America, dude! Learn how to drive!
這是在美國,老兄! 先學會怎麼開車!
Better ''ruck'' tomorrow!
最好明天就去學吧!
- Extreme! - Fucking assholes.
- 刺激! - 該死的混蛋
Fuck.
媽的
Okay.
好的
Be yourself. Don't be nervous.
自信點 別緊張
So, Maria, what's been goin' on?
那個,瑪利亞,最近忙些什麼呢?
l actually had a very long week at work. How about you?
整整忙了一周的工作,你呢?
Work was good. l caught up on some sleep.
工作還不錯, 能找到一些空閒
Plus, the guy who works next to me decided to bathe for a change.
還有,我旁邊的同事決定跳槽換工作
Really?
真的嗎?
So what are you up to tonight?
那你今晚準備幹些什麼呢?
Actually, l'm just gonna be sitting on my ass,
事實上,只能呆在家
probably eat a whole pint of H?agen-Dazs
大概會在看>的時候
while l watch Blirnd Date.
吃許多哈根達斯
Well, that sounds awful.
噢,看起來挺糟糕
lf you want some company,
如果你需要一些同伴
maybe you can come over and sit on your ass at my place.
可以到我的地方來坐坐
That sounds nice.
聽起來不錯
Bye.
拜
Bye. Bye.
拜  拜
Kumar.
卡瑪
Yo.
唷
Yo, Kumar.
唷,卡瑪
Yo, l'm in here, dude.
唷,我在這兒,老兄
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
嘿,你究竟在幹些什麼?
l'm trimming my pubes.
我在清理我的陰毛
Why aren't you doing this in your room, man?
為什麼不在你的房間媟F這個,夥計
The mirror's in here. Hey, check it out. lt's like a bonsai tree.
鏡子在這 嘿,看看,像不像棵盆景樹
Hey!
嘿!
Besides, man, it makes your johnson look totally bigger.
還有,夥計,這樣能讓你的傢伙看起來更大
Please!
拜託!
Are those my scissors? Dude, l trim my nose hair with those!
那是我的剪刀嗎? 老兄,我用這個來剪鼻毛!
Dude, l've been cutting my ass hair with them for the past six months.
老兄,我已經用這個剪了六個月的屁毛
Get out! Get out of my room.
出去! 從我的房間出去
Kumar. it's Daddy.
卡瑪,我是老爸
l lhope your irnterview today was good.
希望你今天面試愉快
l'm callirng to remirnd you tlhat you lhave arnotlher orne tomorrow
我打電話提醒你明天還有另一個面試
witlh Dr. Weirn from Corrnell at 1 0 a.m. Do rnot be late.
上午10點和科奈爾醫學院的威恩博士 別遲到了
- Hook it up, bi-yatch. - Let's do it.
- 一邊去吧, 老頭子. - 我們開始吧.
Fuck!
靠!
lrn torniglht's top story. a clheetalh escaped earlier today
今晚頭條 一頭印度豹今天早些時候
from tlhe Morristowrn Zoo.
從莫里斯鎮動物園逃出
Oh, nice. Sixteern Carndles is on, man.
我，不錯. 正在上映《十六根蠟燭》, 老兄.
And the award for the least heterosexual statement
下面這個獎頒發給這個公寓堻怳p的一個
ever made in this apartment goes to...Harold Lee.
聲明自己是異性戀的同志-----哈羅得 李
Come on down, man. Take a bow.
老兄，快下來，鞠躬領獎啊
Shut up, man. lt's a classic.
閉嘴！ 這個片子很經典
lt's a very beautiful story about someone
這是個講述一個沒人注意
who feels unnoticed, unappreciated, unloved, you know?
沒人欣賞、沒人愛的人的美麗故事。 知道嗎你?
- Turn it. - lt's a good one, though.
- 換 - 其實是很不錯的.
Homo.
Homo.
Come orn. dude. Just take orne lhit.
來吧,老兄 來一根
Dorn't you warnrna be cool?
你不想變酷嗎?
Hey. marn. wlhat are you doirn'?
嘿,夥計,你在幹什麼?
l'm so lhiglh!
我好爽啊!
Notlhirng carn lhurt me.
沒什麼能傷害我
No!
不要!
- Marijuarna kills. - l love that shit.
- 大麻殺了他 - 我喜歡這種狗屁
We're so high right now.
我們現在太爽了
We're not low.
精神亢奮
Dude, l don't know about you, but l'm fuckin' hungry as balls.
老兄,不知道你怎麼樣 我現在餓得一塌糊塗
No shit, dude. Let's eat.
沒關係,老兄 我們去吃點什麼
No, l don't feel like delivery tonight.
不,我今晚不想叫外賣
- What about KFC? - We've been there too many times.
- 去肯德基怎麼樣? - 我們去那兒太多次了
l want something we haven't had in a while.
我想來點最近我們沒吃過的
Something different, something that'll really hit the spot.
一些不同的, 恰到好處的食物
l want the perfect food.
我想要完美的食物
Are you lhurngry?
你餓了嗎?
Tlhern come to Wlhite Castle arnd try our Slyder Special...
那就來白色城堡 嘗嘗我們最新的特別套餐...
Six burgers. fries. arnd a soft drirnk for ornly $2.99.
六個漢堡包,加炸薯條,還有一杯軟 飲料,一起只要2.99美元
lmagirne all tlhose burgers irn your stomaclh riglht rnow.
想像一下六個漢堡包正在你的胃
Dorn't you like food tlhat's tasty arnd delicious?
你難道不喜歡美味可口的食物嗎?
l do.
我喜歡
Tlhern wlhat are you waitirng for?
那你現在還等什麼?
Head over to Wlhite Castle. lt's wlhat you crave.
馬上來白色城堡 滿足你的渴望
You sure you know how to get there?
你確信知道怎麼去那兒嗎?
l haven't been to White Castle in ages.
我有幾年沒有去過白色城堡了
Dude, l'm telling you, there's one right by that multiplex in New Brunswick.
老兄, 我跟你說, 在新不倫瑞克的 百貨市場那就有一家連鎖店
Nice.
妙極了
- Rosenberg! - Goldstein!
- 羅森柏格! - 金斯坦!
Yo, Manny and Shevitz, get up. We're going to White Castle.
唷,好一對傢伙,起來了 我們去白色城堡
No, we're watching Tlhe Gift on HBO.
不,我們在看電視
No, no, no. No watching. We're starving.
不,不,不,別看了,我們餓得要死
Hey, put that back.
嘿,放回去
No eating until we get to White Castle. Let's roll.
到白色城堡之前別吃東西,我們出發吧
Sorry, kids, we ain't going nowhere.
抱歉,孩子們 我們哪兒也不去
Supposedly Katie Holmes shows her titties in this movie.
按照推測,凱蒂在這部片子堶n露乳頭了
ls that all you Jews ever think about--tits?
你們猶太人成天就想著這些--乳頭嗎?
Katie Holmes is a nice, respectable, wholesome girl.
凱蒂 福爾摩斯是個令人尊敬的健康好女孩
And l'm gonna see her boobs.
我一定要看到她的咪咪.
The things l would eat out of her ass--you have no idea!
我完全被她的屁股迷住了 --你不會知道的!
That is a completely vulgar statement.
這是個很平實的說法.
So is ''l want to bang Britney Spears on the bathroom floor.''
就象 ''我一直想在浴室地板上搞小甜甜布蘭尼''
But it's true.
但這是真的
Touch¨¦.
說的不錯.
Hey, listen, if--
嗨, 聽著, 如果--
l think Kumar's a faygele.
我覺著卡瑪是個玻璃.
They're totally gay for each other.
他們完全是在搞同性戀
- Hey, you wanna suck on this? - Uh-huh.
- 嘿,你要吸點這個嗎? - 嗯
What the hell are you bringing your bag for?
你幹嘛要帶著你的包出來?
Try to get some work done in the car.
設法在車塈髡阬I工作
- Here, you're driving. - Shit, l forgot my cell phone.
- 鑰匙給你,你開車 - 操,我忘了帶手機
You wanna run back and get it?
你要跑回去拿嗎?
No, we've gone too far.
不,我們走太遠了
Hey, there's your girlfriend.
嘿,你女朋友在那兒
You gonna talk to her this time,
這次你是要跟她聊幾句,
or are you gonna be a Vagina McGinastein about it?
還是永遠做個縮頭烏龜?
What the hell are you doing?
你到底在幹嘛?
You could've asked her if she wanted to come to White Castle with us.
你也許可以問她願不願意 跟我們一起去白色城堡
- Hold the elevator. Wait! - Hey, how are--
- 電梯,等下! - 嘿,你好--
You're worthless.
你真沒用
l'm not worthwhile.
我不值得去做
Just fucking talk to her once. lt won't be weird anymore.
只要跟她談一次 就不會這麼尷尬了
Look, it doesn't matter.
瞧,沒關係
The only girls who are interested in me are girls l have no interest in.
鍾情于我的女孩 我卻對她沒有興趣
Like Cindy Kim.
比如金辛蒂
Speaking of Cindy, she called earlier.
說到辛蒂, 她早些時候來電話了
One of those Asian clubs she's in is throwing a party at her dorm tonight.
她加入的一個亞洲人俱樂部 今晚在她宿舍舉行派對
God, she invites me to everything.
天啊,她什麼事情都邀請我
So what? She's kind of fuckin' cute. Let her touch your penis.
那又怎麼樣?她多可愛 讓她上你吧
Oh, look.
噢,看啊
lt's the Brothers McFag.
是同性戀兄弟
Let me guess--the one with the purse is the catcher.
讓我猜猜--拿包的那個是“打擊者”.
Come on, guys, let's get ourselves some fucking Mountain Dew.
來吧，小子們，我們一塊喝點烈的威士卡吧.
Extreme!
刺激!
Yeah, extreme assholes.
沒錯, 刺激的臭小子們.
Why do l have to be the catcher?
為什麼我要當“打擊者”?
Dude, forget about those pricks. Let's just get some food.
老兄,忘了那些屌人 全心全意去吃東西吧
l am so hungry. l'm gonna eat, like, 20 of those burgers, man.
我太餓了,我將要吃掉 20個那樣的漢堡,夥計
Dude, fuckin' l will see your 20 burgers and raise you 5 orders of fries.
老兄,我會看你吃下20個, 並且還幫你買5包炸薯條
Dude, give me 35 cents.
老兄,給我35美分
What's going on? lt didn't register.
怎麼了?沒用
- What? - Give me 35 more cents.
- 什麼? - 再給我35美分
- l don't have any more change. - Should l just go through?
- 我沒有零錢了 - 我就這樣闖過這媔?
No, no, l don't like breaking the law.
不,不,我不想違法
Yeah, l can see that.
是啊,我能懂
Hey, move your ass!
嘿,快點滾開!
- l'm sorry. Hold on. - l'm going through.
- 對不起,等一下 - 我要闖了
No, don't. No. No. Hold on.
不,不要 不,不,等下
Let me walk to a manned tollbooth and l'll tell them what happened.
讓我去人工收費亭那告訴他們發生了什麼
- Sorry! - Move, you fuckin' twat!
- 抱歉! - 快走開,混蛋!
- What's the fuckin' holdup here? - Shit.
- 這堻Q什麼鬼東西堵住了? - 操
Move, you retarded cocksucker! Move!
滾開, 你們兩個白癡! 滾開!
- Are you crazy? - What?
- 你瘋了嗎? - 什麼?
What are you doing? Why you throwing the weed out?!
你在幹什麼? 為什麼把大麻扔出去了?!
- The cops are gonna catch us. - No, they're not. Not for that.
- 巡警會抓住我們的 - 不,他們不會,不會為了那個
- Take this exit. - What?
- 走這個出口 - 什麼?
- Take this exit! - No!
- 走這個出口! - 不!
Dude!
老兄!
You know, that was the last of our weed.
你知道, 那是我們最後的一點大麻了
Sorry. l get a little paranoid sometimes.
抱歉,有時候我有一點妄想狂症狀
Now we're in Newark, of all places.
現在我們到了這個 臭名昭著的鬼地方
You know we're gonna get shot.
你知道我們會被槍殺的
Maybe it's not as bad as they say. Maybe it's just a bunch of hype.
可能不像人們說的那麼糟糕 可能只是一個騙局
Check it out. Those guys look like a lame version of us.
看啊,那些傢伙好像沒看到我們
- Holy shit!
- 操他媽的!
Let's get the fuck outta here.
快離開這個鬼地方
- Go! Go! Drive! Drive! - Yeah, that was your fault.
- 快!快!加速!加速! - 那是你的錯
- Fuck you.
- 操你
Yo, check it out. We're almost there.
唷,看啊,我們快到了
Thank God. l'm starving.
謝天謝地,我快餓死了
- Hello, New Brunswick! - Prepare to gorge yourself.
- 你好,新不倫瑞克! - 準備大吃一頓了
You know-- We need some tunage for this.
你知道-- 我們需要來點音樂
Presets. Use the presets.
我放好了,放我預先裝置的那些
Oh, come on, dude, your whole life is preset.
噢,老兄 你生命堜狾釭F西都是預先裝置的
Try something new.
來點新鮮的
Where is this place? lsn't it supposed to be right around here?
這是哪兒? 白色城堡不是就在這附近嗎?
- Chill. We'll find it. - Wait a second--is that the multiplex?
- 掃興,我們會找到它的 - 等下---那個是百貨商場嗎?
- Yes. - Sweet!
- 是的 - 妙極了!
That means the White Castle should be right around the corner.
那意味著白色城堡就在這個轉角
What the hell is going on, Kumar?
卡瑪,到底怎麼回事?
That does not look like a White Castle to me.
我看那個不太像是白色城堡
Uh-uh. Dude, we gotta check this out.
啊哈 老兄,我們必須去看一看
Hey, look here, fellas. You guys gonna have to order from the drive-thru menu.
嘿,看這,夥計 你們要從車行道排隊預定
What happened to the White Castle?
白色城堡去哪兒了?
What?
什麼?
There used to be a White Castle right here in this location.
這個位置曾經有一個白色城堡
Where is it?
它在哪兒?
l hate to be the bearer of bad news, guys,
我不願告訴你們壞消息,兄弟
but Burger Shack, they bought this location about four years ago.
Shack漢堡店四年前買了這個地方
God!
天啊!
Please tell me there's another White Castle in town.
請告訴我城堶兒還有白色城堡?
- No. - Are you sure?
- 沒有 - 你確信?
Do l look like the kind of brother
我看起來像那種
that would be unsure about something like that?
對那些事情還不確信的傢伙嗎?
Shit! What are we gonna do?
操! 那我們怎麼辦?
l don't know, man. Should we just eat here?
我不知道,我們應該就在這婺悃M嗎?
Hey. Psst.
嘿,喂
There's a White Castle that's open 24 hours up in Cherry Hill.
在徹塈ざ蜃磽酗@家24小時白色城堡店
lt's about 45 minutes from here.
離這有45分鐘車程
l can make the trip if you're willing to.
如果你想去我開車
Kumar, l got a shitload of work to finish.
卡瑪,我有一大堆的工作要完成
You got that med school interview.
你明天還有醫學院的面試
Forget about the med school interview. lt's a non-issue.
別提那個面試了 那無關緊要
What do you mean it's a non-issue?
什麼叫無關緊要?
Ding-dong! May l interject for a second?
叮-咚! 我能插一句話嗎?
As a Burger Shack employee for the past three years,
作為三年來Shack漢堡店的員工,
if there's one thing l've learned, it's that if you're craving White Castle,
如果有一件事我學到了, 那就是假如你渴望去白色城堡,
the burgers here just don't cut it.
這堛犖~堡絕對不能滿足你
ln fact, just thinking about those tender little White Castle burgers
事實上, 只要想一下那些溫柔嬌小 白色城堡的漢堡包
with those little, itty-bitty grilled onions
夾著細碎的烤洋蔥
that just explode in your mouth like flavor crystals
像風味水晶一樣在你的嘴媄z發
every time you bite into one...
每咬上一口...
...just makes me want to burn this motherfucker down.
...就讓我想要把這個 不要臉的地方燒為平地
Come on, Pookie, let's burn this motherfucker down!
來吧,波奇, 讓我們不要臉的地方燒為平地!
Come on, Pookie! Let's burn it, Pookie!
來吧,波奇! 燒了它,波奇!
Let's burn this motherfucker down!
讓我們不要臉的地方燒為平地!
Let's burn it down! Let's burn it!
燒光它! 燒了它!
So you guys maybe should just suck it up and go to White Castle.
夥計,你們真應該馬上去白色城堡
You can always get your work done in the car.
你總能在車塈髡角u作
- Let's do it. - All right. Awesome.
- 我們去吧 - 好的,棒極了
Then listen, listen--no matter what, we are not ending this night
聽著,聽著---不管怎樣 今晚我們沒吃到白色城堡的漢堡
without White Castle in our stomachs.
就絕不甘休
- Agreed? - Agreed.
- 同意嗎? - 同意
Wise choice.
明智的選擇
You guys might have wanted to stay away
你們差點就嘗到了
from our special sauce tonight.
我們今晚的特別沙司
Me and Pookie, we added a secret ingredient.
波奇和我, 我們加了一種特別配料
l'll give you a hint.
給你一個提示
lt's semen.
精液
Animal semen.
動物精液
Dude, remember when Goldstein used to work at that burger place?
老兄,記得金斯坦曾經 在這個漢堡店工作過嗎?
This is the most fucking confusing movie l've ever seen--
這是我看過最糟糕的電影了--
she's possessed, she's not possessed.
該瘋狂的時候，她不瘋狂
Dude, that rack better be stacked.
那種折磨還應該可以妖豔點兒
- Tits! Tits! - Boobies, boobies, boobies.
- 乳頭!乳頭! - 咪咪, 咪咪, 咪咪.
Holy shit! Whoa!
操他媽的! 喔!
Those aren't real. Yes, they are.
太他媽假了！ 但確實是真的。
You know, l'm almost completely sober right now.
你知道,我們現在太沉悶了
l wish we had some more weed.
真希望還有一些大麻
Sorry.
抱歉
Princeton.
普林斯頓
- We're getting off here. - Why?
- 我們在這下車 - 為什麼?
Because we're gonna sweet-talk Cindy Kim into finding us some weed.
我們可以哄金辛蒂 幫我們搞到一些大麻
- No. - Why not?
- 不行 - 為什麼不?
You talk to her on the phone all the time.
你經常和她通電話
She calls me. Then she rambles on
她打給我的 然後長談一些
about her East Asian Students Club or whatever.
關於她的東亞學生俱樂部或者什麼
Then l have to actually pretend that l give a shit
然後我不得不胡扯一通
or else she calls me a Twinkie.
否則她就叫我是Twinkie.
A what?
叫你什麼?
Twinkie--yellow on the outside, white on the inside.
Twinkie--皮是黃的，心是白的.
Look, you Twinkie bitch,
聽著，你這個Twinkie,
you were the one that threw our weed out the window, okay?
是你把我們的好東西扔到窗外的?
So we're going to Princeton,
所以我們要去普林斯頓,
and it's your responsibility to make sure we're high as shit
並且你有責任讓我們
by the time we're eating those burgers.
在準備要吃漢堡包時 爽的一塌糊塗
Forget it. End of discussion.
別想了. 討論結束.
l am not seeing Cindy Kim.
我不會去見金辛蒂的.
Harold, l'm so glad you showed up.
哈樂德,很高興你露面了
Yeah, me too.
是的,我也是
Did you like the hibiscus petals l glued to the envelope l sent you?
你喜歡我粘在信封上的 芙蓉花嗎?
Yeah, they were nice.
當然,它們很漂亮
Hey, dude, you know where l can get some green?
嘿,老兄,你知道哪兒 可以買到綠色物品?
Dude, you know where l can get some chronic?
老兄,知道哪兒能買到慢性品?
Jesus, what the hell kind of lvy League school is this?
上帝,這究竟是什麼常青藤聯盟大學?
Man.
夥計
Over here, man.
過來,夥計
You lookin' to toke up?
你想要來一口嗎?
- Yes. - Yes?
- 是的 - 是嗎?
Thank Christ. Just give me a dime of your finest sticky.
謝天謝地,給我來點最好的
You wanna see sticky-icky, my friend?
你要看一下嗎，兄弟?
Oh, my God!
噢，我的天!
Whoa, man!
喔,夥計!
Don't touch, man. That's not cool.
別碰它,夥計 這樣做不好
You can't--
你不能--
Jeez! This is my baby!
呀! 這是我的寶貝!
Yes?
好的?
Kenneth Park, class of 2004.
派克-肯尼斯, 2004級的
- Hi.
- 你好
ls it true you're an analyst for Brewster Keegan?
你真的是布盧斯-奇根的分析家嗎?
Yes, l'm a junior analyst.
是的,我是初級分析員
Awesome!
厲害!
l told you, he's good.
我告訴過你,他不錯
- Yes. - This is actually a two-part question.
- 好的 - 這是第二部分的問題
l'm applying for a summer internship at Brewster Keegan.
我正在申請布盧斯-奇根的暑期實習
l was wondering, a) what's it like being an investment banker,
我想知道, a) 投資銀行家是怎樣的職業?
and b) would you write me a recommendation?
b) 你願意幫我寫推薦信嗎?
Here. That's sixt--80 bucks.
給你,要6-80美元
- 80 bucks? - Yeah, 80 bucks.
- 80美元? - 是的,80美元
Yo, this is worth 40 tops, bro.
唷,這頂多值40美元,兄弟
''Bro''? l'm not your bro, bro.
"兄弟"? 我不是你的兄弟,兄弟
Okay, and that's 80 bucks.
好吧,80美元
You don't feel like getting high tonight?
今晚你不想爽嗎?
lf you don't feel like getting high, that's cool with me,
如果你不想爽, 這個就留在我這吧
because there's lots of people around here. See this guy?
因為這埵陶\多人想要 看到這個傢伙了?
Hey, loser.
嘿,失敗者
Hey, what's up, George? l smoke buds with George all the time.
嘿,最近怎麼樣,喬治? 我經常和喬治一起吸大麻
What kind of hippie are you?
你是哪種嬉皮士?
What kind of hippie am l? Man, l'm a business hippie.
我是哪種嬉皮士? 夥計,我是做生意的嬉皮士
l understand the concept of supply and demand.
我明白供求的概念
''What's it like being an investment banker?''
''投資銀行家是怎樣的職業?''
To be honest with you, it's actually pretty aw...
老實跟你說, 這實際上是非常...
...awesome.
...令人敬畏的職業
Excellent!
極好的!
As for the recommendation, l guess l can make a couple calls.
至於推薦信, 或許我能幫忙打幾個電話
Actually, Harold, we should be getting to the party.
實際上, 哈樂德, 我們應該去派對了
We can discuss all this stuff on the way there.
我們能在去的路上談這些
- lt's just down the hall. - Okay.
- 就在下面的大廳 - 好吧
l'm sorry. l can't go. l have to wait for Kumar.
對不起,我不能去 我必須得等卡瑪
You'll see him when we're done.
我們結束了你會看到他的
Trust me, you're gonna love this.
相信我, 你會喜歡這個的
Kenny's mom dropped off a big pot of kimchi jigae.
肯尼的媽媽送來了許多朝鮮泡菜
lt's really good. lt's delicious.
真的非常好 很美味
Yeah?
是嗎?
That's nice.
那不錯
- 80 bucks, okay? - Okay.
- 80美元,好吧? - 好的
- Hello. - Are you guys about to smoke?
- 嗨 - 你們要吸煙嗎?
Yes, we're gonna smoke. Do you wanna come back to my place?
是的,我們要吸煙, 你們願意來我的地方一起嗎
Please, like they want to go listen to a bunch of Phish records
省省吧，跟你的蹩腳的詩比起來
while you read your lame-ass poetry.
她們更想聽Phish的唱片.
Girls, you guys wanna hang out,
女生們, 你們願不願意一塊出去,
maybe smoke a little weed and have some fun?
抽點兒煙，找點樂子?
- All right.
- 好啊
My poetry's not lame. lt's really good.
我的詩真的很好
- Yeah, l'm sure. - lt's great.
- 是的,我確信 - 是很好
We're gonna eat before this gets cold.
我們要在這個冷之前吃完
What you say we meet back in our room in about 20 minutes?
20分鐘後在我們的房間見?
We're in room 109.
我們在109房間
109. Got it. l'll see you ladies later, huh?
109,知道了 我會去拜訪你們的,嗯?
Yes!
耶!
109. We'll see you ladies later. Yes!
109,等下我們會去拜訪,耶!
We're getting laid, bro.
我們有豔遇了,兄弟
All right, l'll see you there, man.
好吧,我會去那兒見你的,夥計
20--20--208?
20--20--208?
208. Yes! 208!
208,是的! 208!
Roldy, dude, you gotta come quick.
老兄,你得快點來
There's these two filthy pussies just aching to get boned by us.
有兩個壞女孩等著我們上呢
l mean, there are these two very lovely young pussies
我的意思是, 有兩個非常可愛的女孩
who would like to have a chat with you and l.
要跟你和我聊天
Sorry. Harold's coming with us.
抱歉,哈樂德跟我們一起的
That's bullshit. He's coming with me. lsn't that right, Roldy?
胡說,他是和我一起來的 對嗎,夥計?
- Let's go to the party. - No, no, no. Fuck that.
- 我們去派對吧 - 不,不,不,
Here. This is Harold's understudy. You can do whatever you want.
這,他是哈樂德的替身 你可以做任何事情你想做的
Roldy, let's go.
我們走吧
Sorry.
抱歉
l can't believe you were gonna ditch me for the Joy Luck Club.
我不敢相信你竟然要拋棄我 去那種無聊的俱樂部
You know what their parties are like.
你知道他們的派對會是多麼無聊
What do you want me to say? l was under pressure.
你要我說什麼呢? 我是被逼的
Just say no. That's all it takes. Here.
直接說“不”就行了 來一口
All right, take a hit of that.
好吧
What's going on up there?
那兒在幹什麼?
Barracuda to Sparrow, Barracuda to Sparrow.
Barracuda呼叫Sparrow, Barracuda呼叫Sparrow
We got two high-fliers on level three.
我們在三樓發現了兩個吸煙者
l just wanna talk!
我要跟你們談談!
Dude, in here, in here.
老兄,進這,進這
Women!
女廁!
What if someone finds us in here?
有人發現我們在這怎麼辦?
Chill the fuck out. He's not gonna look for us in the girls' bathroom.
別擔心, 他不會闖進女衛生間來找我們的
Shit! Come here.
操!來這
lt worked on me. There's no reason it shouldn't work on you.
那個對我有效, 不知道為什麼對你沒有效果
But your breasts look beautiful.
但你的胸部看起來很漂亮
l just want those cute little ping-pong breasts.
我只想要像 小乒乓球一樣可愛的胸部
You know, that kind of go...
你知道, 那種類型的...
Hurry up because l want to go smoke weed
快點,我想要去吸點大麻
with that dishy lndian guy.
和那個有魅力的印度人一起
lt's gonna be a few minutes.
幾分鐘就好
l'm about to have the worst case of taco shits.
我要把那些壞的 玉米麵豆卷都拉出來
Oh, God.
哦,上帝
Great, l think l've got to go, too.
天啊,我想我也要蹲會
Hey, Clarissa, do you want to play battle shits?
嘿,卡拉麗莎,想來打屎仗嗎?
- Oh, my God! - Battle shits?
- 噢,我的天! - 屎仗?
We haven't played that since back at camp.
我們很久沒玩過了
l know, l know. Wait for it.
我知道,我知道 等一下
Hit.
命中
Scag! You sank my destroyer!
靠! 你把我的“驅逐艦”擊沉了!
Fuck!
操!
l can't take it anymore!
我不能再忍受了!
Christy, are you still there?
克利斯蒂, 你還在那兒嗎?
Damn! You sank my battle shit!
該死! 你把我這一仗全毀了!
Shit.
狗屁
Dude!
老兄!
She said in 20-10?
她說是在20-10?
Have you seen a Korean guy around here?
你在這附近看到過一個韓國人嗎?
Yeah, only when l open my eyes, though.
是的,我睜開眼就看到了
'Tard.
那個tard
20-1 1 .
20-11
Yo, this party's bumpin'!
喲，這個聚會還挺強嘛!
- Who wants some Buda? - Yeah!
- 誰要一些泡菜? - 耶!
Holy shit! Kenneth Park, class of 2004.
假的吧!派克-肯尼斯,2004級的
Dude, l'm thinking you really screwed up by not coming to this party.
老兄,我肯定你現在很後悔沒來這個派對
l screwed up?
我後悔?
Can we have some pot brownies?
我們能來點“泡菜”嗎?
l don't know. l'm running a little low.
我不知道，剩的不多了
A titty flash might persuade me.
讓我瞄一眼乳頭可能我會答應.
- Should we? - l think you should.
- 一定要麼? - 是的.
Okay.
好吧.
- Whoa.
- 喔唔
Hey, you!
嘿,你們!
Shit!
操!
Hey!
嘿!
- Hey! - Let's get 'em! Halt!
- 嘿! - 抓住他們,停下!
- Hey.
- 嗨
- Harold! Harold! - No, no, no.
- 哈樂德!哈樂德! - 不,不,不
- Hey, dude! - Come here!
- 嗨,老兄! - 讓開!
Well, well, well.
好的,好的
- What do we have here? - Oh, no! That's my baby!
- 這埵酗偵? - 噢,不! 那是我的寶貝!
Hold his throat and groin. Come on, rookie.
抓住他的喉嚨和腹部 快點,新手
Should we go back for the weed?
我們應該回去拿大麻嗎?
Are you crazy? Run! Run!
你瘋了嗎? 跑!快跑!
l can't believe it, man. We were this close to getting laid.
真不能相信,夥計 我們差點就有豔遇了
Oh, dude, you always exaggerate.
噢,老兄,你總是誇大其詞
The diarrhea twins definitely would have had sex with us.
那對腹瀉姐妹明顯的要跟我們上床
What about Cindy? She was looking kinda cute tonight, man.
辛蒂怎麼樣? 她今晚看起來有幾分可愛,夥計
Cindy's fine. lt's just...
辛蒂還好 只是...
- Just what? - We--
- 只是什麼? - 我們--
Oh, you'd rather have Maria.
噢,你更想得到瑪利亞
Look, it doesn't matter.
瞧,這不重要
l'm gonna end up with Cindy Kim whether l like it or not.
不管我喜不喜歡金辛蒂, 我們都要結束了
Can we just drop this and get our asses to White Castle, man?
我們這樣走下去能到白色城堡嗎?
Fine. Maria.
當然 瑪利亞
What are you doing?
你要幹什麼?
Daddy needs to urinate.
老爹需要小便
Hurry up!
快點!
l'm serious. Don't take all night.
我是認真的 別尿一晚上
All right.
好吧
- Excuse me, l have to-- - Huh?
- 對不起, 我必須得-- - 哼?
l have to ask you. Why are you peeing right here?
我必須得問你 為什麼你要在這塈?
What?
什麼?
l mean, why'd you pee right next to me
我是說,你為什麼要在我旁邊小便
when you could choose that bush or...
你可以選擇那邊的矮樹叢或者...
This is a good bush to pee on.
這片矮樹叢很適合尿尿
Why are you peeing on it?
你為什麼在這塈?
Well, no one was here when l chose this bush.
嗯,我來的時候這堥S人
Oh.
噢
So you get to pee on it and no one else does? Huh?
那只能你一個人尿,不准別人了嗎?嗯?
- No, l just-- - This your bush?
- 不,我只是--- - 這是你的矮樹叢?
You have a special bond with this bush?
你對這片矮樹叢有特別使用權嗎?
- No, l just thought that-- - You the king of the forest?
- 不,我只是認為那個--- - 你是這片樹林的國王嗎?
- l'm sorry? - What?
- 我很抱歉? - 什麼?
Are you a fuckin' tree-hugger? ls this your special bush?!
你是他媽的樹王嗎? 這是你的特別樹叢嗎?!
Never mind. Forget it. l really don't feel like getting stabbed tonight.
別介意,忘了它,我今晚不想被行刺
Nice pubes.
漂亮的陰毛
Thanks.
謝謝
Do you even know where you're going?
你知道現在是往哪兒走嗎?
l'm gonna be honest, l'm a little lost, but, you know,
老實講,我有點迷路了,但是,你知道
once we get back on the highway, we'll be there soon, don't worry.
一旦我們回到了公路上, 就快到了,別著急
We'd better.
最好是這樣
Shit. Now it's raining.
操,開始下雨了
Put on your wipers.
打開雨刷
What are you talking about? lt's just a little mist.
說什麼呢?只是有一點薄霧
Yeah, mist, hence the mist setting.
是的,薄霧,那就把霧刷打開
lt's a safety issue, okay? There we go.
這樣安全一點,是嗎? 就這樣
Thank you, Mr. Wizard. What crawled up your ass?
謝謝你,男巫先生 幹嘛這麼火大?
l'm completely on edge right now, man.
我快崩潰了,夥計
After all the shit that we've been through tonight,
經過今晚的一切
l don't know how much more l can take.
我不知道還能忍受多久
Oh, shit! How the fuck did that get in here?
噢,操!這個鬼東西從哪兒上來的!
Oh, shit!
噢,操!
He bit me! l've got rabies!
它咬我! 我得狂犬症了!
Oh, my God!
噢,我的天!
Dude, get that fuckin' cancer raccoon away from me!
老兄,把這個該死的浣熊扔出去!
Open my window!
打開我這邊的窗戶!
Fuck you, raccoon!
操你,浣熊!
What the Christ?
我的天
- Shit!
- 操!
Jesus! You all right?
上帝啊,你還好吧?
l don't know.
我不知道
Shit.
操
Shit, dude, he's coming over here.
操,他們走過來了,老兄
Probably some old blind bitch!
一些瞎眼的婊子!
- What the fuck are you doing? - We're sorry. We're very sorry!
- 你們他媽的在幹什麼? - 我們很抱歉,非常抱歉!
- Holy shit! - Goldstein?
- 操你媽的! - 金斯坦?
Dude, it's Rold and Kumar.
老兄,是哈樂德和卡瑪
Shit. What's going on, man?
操,發生什麼了,夥計
- What's up, dude? What's up? - All right.
- 怎麼了,老兄,怎麼了 - 沒事
What the hell are you guys doing here?
你們在這媟F什麼呢?
We got the munchies, so we decided we'd go to Hot Dog Heaven.
我們有些餓了, 要去熱狗天堂.
How about you? How was White Castle?
你們怎麼樣? 剛從白色城堡回來嗎?
We haven't gotten there yet. l think l may have rabies.
我們還沒到那兒 我可能得了狂犬症
Yo, dude, how were Katie Holmes' tits?
唷,老兄,凱蒂的乳頭怎麼樣了?
- You know the Holocaust? - Yeah.
- 你知道 大毀滅 嗎? - 是啊.
Picture the exact opposite of that.
跟那個畫面整相反
Nice.
不錯.
Boy, do you need a girl.
夥計,想要一個女孩嗎
lf you guys got the yellow fever,
如果你們急不可待
there's a rockin' Asian party down at Princeton.
在普林斯頓有一個火爆的亞洲人派對
Dude, l got the yellow plague.
老兄,我太饑渴了
There's nothing sexier than a hot Asian chick!
沒什麼比一個熱辣的亞洲妹更性感了!
Asian tits-- l wanna squeeze 'em!
亞洲乳頭-- 我要擠她們
Stop. Don't do that. Please, do not touch me.
停下,別這麼做 拜託,別碰我
l'm very woozy.
我很虛弱
l think l have to go to the hospital.
我必須得去醫院
You should go to Beth lsrael.
你應該去Beth Israel
- We gotta hit up this Asian joint. - No, we don't.
- 我們必須參加這個亞洲人派對 - 不,我們不去
We got to go to Hot Dog Heaven. No more detours along the way.
我們要趕去熱狗天堂 一路上不繞道
- This is what l'm dealing with. - Come on!
- 這是我的意見 - 走吧!
l'm telling you, hit up the Asian party.
我跟你說,去亞洲人的派對
Did you leave the key in the car with the engine running?
你把鑰匙留在車堥S關引擎嗎?
Good luck.
好運
You don't have rabies. We're not going to a hospital. You're fine.
你沒得狂犬症,不必去醫院,你沒事
Uh... Yeah, l don't have rabies.
嗯...是的,沒得狂犬症
Great. Let's just get out of here.
好的,那就離開這塈a
Hey, aren't those the guys that got the shit kicked--
嘿,那些受重傷的傢伙不是--
l know. l know. Let's just go.
我知道,我知道 快走吧
Just go.
走吧
Kumar.
卡瑪
- Hey, it's your dad and brother. - Shit.
- 嘿,是你爸爸和哥哥 - 操
No wonder you didn't want to go to the hospital.
難怪你不願意到醫院來
- Hey, Dad. - Hi, Dr. Patel.
- 嗨,爸爸 - 嗨,派特醫生
- What's up? - Saikat. What's going on?
- 最近好嗎? - Saikat,最近怎麼樣?
l hope you are here to apologize for what you did in your interview today.
我希望你在這堹酮陘竣悛滬掘桯D歉
What the hell's wrong with you, Kumar?
你究竟怎麼了,卡瑪?
God! You're 22 years old. When are you gonna grow up
上帝!你都22歲了 什麼時候才能長大
and stop this post-college rebel bullshit?
能停止這種無聊的反抗行為
- Like your life is so hard. - Eat my balls, Saikat.
- 你的生活作風讓人討厭 - Saikat,閉上你的嘴
l will not tolerate this business from you any longer.
我再也不能忍受你了
You have one more interview tomorrow morning,
你明天還有一次面試
and if l hear from Dr. Wein that you were anything short of spectacular,
如果我從威恩醫生那聽不到好消息
l'll completely cut you off.
我將完全不給你生活費
- Dad, come on. - Daddy is not coming on anything.
- 爸爸,別這樣 - 爸爸不是萬能的
You will be there, and you will behave.
你要給我去表現好點
l have put too much time and energy into you
我對你已經花費了太多的時間和精力
to let you go and fuck it all up!
以後不再管你了,隨你怎麼樣!
You're absolutely right. l'm sorry, guys.
你們完全正確,抱歉
Wow, l'm sorry.
對不起
Sorry. lt won't happen again, okay?
不會再發生這種事了,好嗎?
Good.
不錯
l will speak with you tomorrow.
明天我會跟你談談
- Bye, Harold. - Bye.
- 拜,哈樂德 - 拜
See ya.
再見
Wow, man.
喔,夥計
l guess you're going to med school after all, eh?
你終究還是要去醫學院,嗯?
Fuck that, dude. Like l care what my dad thinks.
別說了,老兄 我像是在乎爸爸想法的人嗎
l can't wait to see the look on his face
我等不及想看到他的面孔
when he finds out l didn't go to my interview tomorrow.
當他發現我沒去明天的面試時
lf he wants to cut me off, fine. l don't need his money.
如果他不給我生活費,好吧 我就不要他的錢
l don't understand. You just hugged him.
我不明白,你剛和他們擁抱
Yeah, l just needed to get my hands on this.
是的,我只想拿到這個
Access card.
通行證
Two words for you, bro-- medical marijuana.
給你兩個單詞, 兄弟-- 醫用 大麻
No.
不
Oh, this is stolen.
噢,這是在偷
lf we get caught, you are taking the blame.
如果我們被抓了,你會被責備的
This is not my idea.
我不想這樣
We're not gonna get caught, okay? We're gonna go get baked
我們不會被抓的,對嗎? 我們去拿點大麻
and then go eat just like we planned. Now, just calm down.
然後按計劃去吃漢堡 現在,只需冷靜
- We gotta find the pharmacy. - Dr. Patel!
- 我們會找到藥房 - 派特醫生!
Thank God l found you. We have an emergency.
謝天謝地找到你們了 我們有一個急診
Nurses, l need these two doctors scrubbed, gloved,
護士,幫忙把這兩位醫生消毒, 帶上手套
and ready for the O.R. stat!
準備手術!
- What the hell is going on? - He probably thinks l'm my brother.
- 到底怎麼回事? - 他可能錯以為我是我哥哥
Just don't worry about it. Leave the talking to me.
別擔心 把話留給我
lt's a godforsaken bloodbath.
是一次淒慘的大屠殺
The patient was brought in by EMS five minutes ago.
病人5分鐘前被救護車送來
As you can see, we have three horrific gunshot wounds.
你能看到, 這有3處可怕的子彈傷口
lt's a good thing l found you two.
找到你們兩個真是太好了
All the other surgeons are working on other patients.
其他的外科醫生都在做手術
No, there's been a mistake.
不,有個誤會
What Dr. Lee is trying to say is that we need to sedate the patient...
李醫生是說我們需要給病人 服用安定劑...
- ...or he could go into cardiac arrest. - All right, l'll get the anesthesiologist.
- ...否則心跳將要停止 - 好的,我去拿麻醉藥
Hang on a second, nurse. What we should probably use is marijuana.
等一下,護士,我們要的是大麻
That'll sufficiently sedate the patient for surgery.
那個會很好的讓病人安定
Marijuana?
大麻?
But why?
但是為什麼?
We don't have time for questions.
我們沒時間問這個了
We need marijuana now, as much of it as possible!
我們現在需要大麻, 盡可能多的!
Like a big bag of it.
像一大袋那麼多
But, Doctor, we don't have marijuana in this hospital.
但是,醫生,我們這堥S有大麻
Shit.
操
Oh, shit! This guy's gonna die!
噢,操! 這傢伙快死了!
Doctor, you've got to do something or we're gonna lose him!
醫生,你要做點什麼 否則他會死的!
l'm gonna do this the old-fashioned way.
我用老式的方法來幹
Start the nitrous. Give me two large-bore l.V.s
打開氮氣. 給我兩個大鉗子
and start a Ringers lactate push.
再打開調節分泌裝置.
Dr. Roldy, hold this.
Roldy醫生, 按住這.
More gauze, please.
再來點紗布
- Doctor, the patient is desatting. - Dude, he's desatting! He's desatting!
- 醫生, 病人快不能呼吸了 - 老兄, 他不能呼吸了，不能呼吸了!
The patient has a collapsed lung. l need a 1 4-gauge angiocath stat.
病人肺部虛脫. 我需要一個4號的血管針.
- That was genius. - Thank you.
- 天才 - 謝謝你
- Great job! - You guys did it.
- 做的好! - 你們幹的好
No, it's you.
不,是你們
- Sexy. - What'd you say?
- 性感 - 你說什麼?
Nothing.
沒什麼
Sweet-pea.
甜心
The patient appears to be stabilized.
病人似乎穩定了
- Good work, doctors, all around. - Great. One of you clean this up, please.
- 幹的好,所有的醫生們 - 好的,來個人把這堬M理乾淨
- Put the chest tube in. - Meow. You're moist.
- 把胸管放進去 - 喵,你濕了
- l'm not sweating anymore. - You're glistening.
- 我不會再出汗了 - 你在聽
Soft and chocolate lips...
柔軟的巧克力色的唇...
- Could l get a little dab here? - Hush now, hush now.
- 能幫我擦一下嗎? - 安靜,安靜
Excuse me, sir. Do you happen to know
打擾一下,先生 你知道
how to get to the White Castle in Cherry Hill from here?
怎麼去希爾鎮的白色城堡嗎?
Yeah. Take the 33 west and take the Turnpike south,
是的,從南部的收費公路 往西走33英里
and there you are.
就到了
l'm telling you, man, that was amazing!
我跟你說,太驚奇了!
Even your dad would have been impressed, man.
就算你爸爸也會留下深刻的印象
Yeah, it wasn't that bad.
是的,還沒那麼壞
This is perfect. We're back on the road, we got directions, it stopped raining.
好極了,我們回到了公路上 我們有了方向,雨也停了
And guess what, man.
夥計,猜我幹了什麼
- l'm officially done with my work. - Oh, yeah? Nice!
- 我正式的完成了工作 - 噢,是嗎?不錯
l'm telling you, dude, things are finally starting to go our way.
我跟你說,老兄 事情終於走上正軌了
Hey, dude, check it out-- Sixteern Carndles.
嘿,老兄,看啊-- 十六根蠟燭
lsn't that your favorite movie?
那不是你最喜歡看的電影嗎?
Wow, man, that's awesome!
喔,夥計,太好了!
Yo, look who decided to go see it.
唷,看誰在那兒等著進場
Holy shit.
操他媽的
See! You said you two had nothing in common,
瞧!你還說你們沒什麼共同點
but you both have the same lame taste in movies!
但你們對電影的品味卻同樣的糟糕!
Shut up.
閉嘴
Hey, we should ask her if she wants to come to White Castle.
嘿,我們應該問問她願不願意 一起去白色城堡
No. No, no. Forget about it. Just drive.
不,不,不 忘了她,開車吧
Dude, come on. lt's 1 :00 in the morning.
老兄,來吧 現在是早上1:00
We're an hour away from home,
我們離家有一個小時路程
and who do we see but your dream girl standing across the street?
而且在路上看到了你的夢中女孩
Just pretend you're a nerdy Asian version of Tom Hanks
試著做個亞洲版的湯姆-漢克斯
and she's a hot Latina Meg Ryan with bigger tits.
她就是那個有著大胸部的拉丁女郎
The cars are going. Can we go? How about that?
車走了 我們能走嗎?怎麼樣?
- What are you doing? - Excuse me, Maria!
- 你在幹什麼? - 打擾了,瑪利亞!
- Maria! Excuse me for a second!
- 瑪利亞!打擾你一下!
Come here!
來這兒!
No! What the hell are you doing?
不!你到底在幹什麼!
Get your hand off the gas! Shit!
拿開你的手! 操!
- l'm stuck! - Stop turning the wheel!
- 我被卡住了! - 別拐車輪!
- l am stuck! - What do you mean you're stuck?
- 你被卡住了是什麼意思?
Get unstuck!
快鬆開!
- You asshole! - Wha--wha--?
- 你這個混蛋! - 什--什--?
We could have seriously injured ourselves, man!
我們差點就受重傷了,夥計!
Yo, don't blame me, genius.
唷,別怪我,夥計
l'm not the one who decided to run us off the frickin' road, all right?
不是我一個人拿的主意,是嗎?
Let's just get back on the highway, okay?
我們返回公路吧,好嗎?
Fine with me.
沒問題
lt's not funny.
好笑麼？
- Where's my spare tire? - l don't know.
- 我的備用輪胎在哪兒? - 我不知道
Where the hell is my spare tire?
我的備用輪胎到底在哪兒?
Oh, yeah!
噢,是的!
Dude, remember that time we got really stoned
老兄,記得那次我們喝醉了嗎
and started throwing shit off that bridge to see if it would float?
我們把輪胎扔到橋下看能不能浮起來?
What bridge? l don't remem-- What are you talking about?
哪個橋?我不大記-- 你在說什麼?
Oh, shit, that's right. That was with Goldstein.
噢,操,是那樣,和金斯坦在一起那次
We borrowed your car that night. My bad.
我們借了你的車,我的錯
Your bad? What the hell are we gonna do now?
你的錯?那我們現在該怎麼辦?
- Hey! - Hey! Excuse me!
- 嗨! - 嗨! 對不起!
- Hello! Over here! - Excuse me!
- 你好! - 對不起!
You boys need some help?
你們需要幫助嗎?
Thanks for helping us out.
謝謝你幫我們出去
No problem at all.
沒問題
l seen you two stranded out there alone in the dark,
我看到你們兩個在黑暗中無助的樣子,
and l said to myself...
我對自己說...
''What would Jesus do?''
''上帝該做點什麼?''
Have you boys accepted Jesus as your Lord and Savior?
你們信奉基督嗎?
- Yes. - Yeah, he's great. Cool guy.
- 是的 - 是的,他很偉大,很酷
Praise the Lord and pass the ammunition!
感謝上帝讓我熬過戰爭!
Name's Randy, but everybody calls me Freakshow.
我叫蘭迪, 但是每個人都叫我“Freakshow”
My name's Kumar.
我叫卡瑪
How are you, Kunie?
你好,卡尼
- This is Harold. - Hi, Jerald. How are you?
- 這是哈樂德 - 嗨,加羅德,你好嗎?
So where exactly are we going?
我們現在是去哪兒?
Don't you worry about that none. We ain't too far from my place.
別擔心,我們離我的地方不遠
Once we get there, l'll have your ride fixed up in a jiffy.
到了那兒, 我會很快幫你們修好車
Check out those boils on his neck.
看他頸上的那些水皰
You gotta look. One of them's actually pulsating.
你必須看 有一個在有規律的搏動
Shut up. He's right next to me. He can hear you.
閉嘴,他就在我旁邊 他能聽到你
Now there's some sort of puss.
現在有幾個在臉上
- lt's disgusting! - Shut up.
- 太噁心了! - 閉嘴
Just one little boil. Just look at it.
那個小癤子 看啊
See, isn't that the most disgusting thing you've ever seen?
看,是不是你見過最噁心的東西了
Do you think just because you're whispering,
你認為就因為你在耳語
he can't hear what you're saying?
他就聽不到你在說什麼了嗎?
He's two feet away from us. He can hear this entire conversation.
他就在兩步遠 能聽到我們講的一切
He can hear me talking right now.
他能聽到我正在說的
Don't worry about it. He can't hear anything...
別擔心 他什麼都聽不到...
not with all that crust in his ear.
用他那些耳朵堛熊w皮
l heard everything you said.
我聽到了你說的一切
lt's gonna take me a while to fix up your car there,
修好你們的汽車要一點時間
so if you boys like, you can go on inside,
如果你們願意,可以進屋塈之
get yourselves something to drink, wash up,
自己拿點東西喝,清洗一下
fuck my wife, watch TV-- anything you want.
操我妻子, 看電視-- 隨便你想做什麼
Mi casa es su casa.
我的房屋就是你們的房屋
Just don't do anything the Good Lord wouldn't do.
別做上帝不願意做的事
Thank you.
謝謝
We're gonna die. He's going to kill us.
我們會死的 他會殺了我們
Dude, am l deaf, or did he just say we get to fuck his wife?
老兄,我是不是聾了,那傢伙說 讓我們幹他妻子
He couldn't have said that.
他不可能說那些
Who cares? You've seen Freakshow.
誰關心? 你也見過Freakshow了
What do you think his wife is gonna look like?
他的老婆能好到哪兒去?
Oh, hi, boys.
噢,嗨,孩子們
l'm Freakshow's wife Liane.
我是Freakshow的妻子莉安
Can l get you some pink lemonade?
要不要來點檸檬汁?
Why don't you just go have a seat in the living room?
為什麼不去臥室坐坐?
l'll be back in a jiffy.
我一會兒就回來
Thanks.
謝謝
- Hot. Hot! - Uh-huh.
- 辣,辣! - 噢!
Jesus Christ.
上帝
Okay, it's official. We've entered the Twilight Zone.
是啊,我們真的到了貧民區
- Dude, Liane is fucking hot. - She's not ugly.
- 老兄,莉安真是太熱辣了 - 她不醜
Here you go, boys.
給,孩子們
- Thank you. - Thanks a lot.
- 謝謝 - 非常感謝
Liane, how are things between you and Freakshow presently?
莉安,你和Freakshow的關係怎樣
Oh! They've never been better. We love each other so much.
噢! 不能再好了 我們非常愛對方
l was just wondering, how does a guy like Freakshow...
我只想知道, 像Freakshow那樣的傢伙怎麼...
...end up with a girl like you?
...最終和你在一起了?
Well, we met at choir practice about four years ago.
嗯,我們在唱詩班認識的 大約4年前
Freakshow was really shy back then, you know,
Freakshow 那時非常害羞, 你們知道,
'cause of all his hideous boils on his face and neck.
因為那些頸上和臉上的癤子
Sure, sure.
當然,當然
But he had the most amazing voice,
但是他有著最動聽的聲音
like a baby canary.
像一隻小金絲雀一樣
The devil is everywhere
魔鬼處處有
Hey, Randy, what, the devil, huh
嘿,蘭迪, 什麼, 魔鬼,哼
The devil is everywhere
魔鬼處處有
Hey, Randy, what
嘿,蘭迪, 什麼,
After Easter service one day, l told him how much l loved his solo
復活節後的一天, 我告訴他我是多麼喜歡他的單曲
and he finally mustered up the courage to ask me out.
他終於聚起勇氣約我出去
We've been in love ever since.
我們從那時候開始相愛
So, are you boys gonna fuck me now or what?
那麼,你們現在想幹我還是?
Rock, paper, scissors to see who goes first. Ready?
石頭, 剪刀,布 看誰先上,準備好了嗎?
- Rock, paper-- - Wait a second.
- 石頭,剪刀--- - 等片刻
What about Freakshow?
Freakshow怎麼辦?
What? You assume we don't know how to have a good time?
什麼? 我們難道不知道 該怎麼過的快樂嗎?
l just...
我只是...
Never mind. Rock, paper, scissors.
沒關係 石頭,剪刀,布
Sorry, but if you boys want me, you have to do me at the same time.
對不起,如果你們想要我 你們必須得一起上
- Huh? - Come on, give me the double stuff.
- 嗯? - 來吧,給我雙分填充料
l'm not sure we quite understand, Liane.
我們不是很清楚,莉安
l want you both inside me simultaneously.
我要你們同時進入我
- One hole or two? - Whatever you want.
- 一個洞還是兩個? - 隨你們便
Sorry. No, thank you. No, thank you.
抱歉,不,謝謝 不用,謝謝
Dude, if it's two holes, it might not be that bad.
老兄,如果是兩個洞 還不是那麼糟糕
- Shotgun anus. - Forget it!
- 幹肛門 - 別提了!
l don't want our balls rubbing against each other.
我不想要我們的 蛋蛋互相撞來撞曲
- What, are you kidding? - No way! Forget it.
- 什麼,你在開玩笑嗎? - 絕不!忘了吧
How about blow jobs? Can we have blow jobs?
口交怎麼樣? 能口交嗎?
Well, okay.
好的
Come here.
過來
Okay. l'm going up there.
好的,我來了
l wanna come, too.
我也要
- Think you could help me with this? - You need help?
- 你能幫我解開嗎? - 你需要幫忙?
Okay, yeah. lt's a little sticky there.
好的 那兒有點緊
- You can do it. - Okay.
- 你能做到 - 是的
l can do it.
我能做到
Do you wanna play with them?
想要玩它們嗎?
Play with them.
玩..
- Yeah, let's do that. - Okay.
- 好的,讓我們來 - 好的
Let's do that.
我們一起
Well, boys, l fixed your tire.
喂，你們的車胎修好了
Hi, honey.
嗨, 親愛的
What in the hell are you doing with my wife?
你們跟我老婆幹嘛呢
You said outside that we could have sex with her.
你說你在外頭時我們就能 跟你幹你妻子
Shit! Shit!
操!操!
- l most certainly did not. - Yeah, you did.
-但我沒說過 - 不,你說了
- l did not! - You did.
- 沒有! - 說了.
- Oh, no, l didn't! - You did, you did.
- 哦, 不, 我沒有! - 說了, 你說了.
- You sure? - You said it.
- 你肯定? - 你剛剛說過的
My mistake!
那錯怪你們了!
Freakshow.
Freakshow.
Well, since we're all here...
好吧，既然我們都在......
...how about a foursome?
...四個人一起來，怎麼樣?
Who wants the first reach-around?
誰想第一個上?
Okay, let's agree to never talk about what just happened.
好吧，說好了， 剛才的事誰也不准再提
Agreed.
同意
That's a very good idea.
想法不錯
Dude, l have no idea where we are.
我說哥們，我們在哪兒
What?
什麼?
- ls that a hitchhiker? - What the hell?
- 那是個要搭車的嗎? - 你想幹啥?
- Should we pick him up? - And get chopped to bits? Are you crazy?
- 我們是不是讓他上來? - 然後把他砍成碎片? 你瘋了吧?
You know what? We're lost. He may know how to get back on the highway.
你知道什麼? 咱們迷路了. 他可能知道 怎麼回到高速公路上.
Get back on the road. This is my car.
接著開. 這可是我的車.
We are not picking up a hitchhiker, man.
別讓人搭車。
Hey, guys, thanks for picking me up.
嘿，哥門兒們，多謝讓我搭車
Excuse me, are you Neil Patrick Harris?
不好意思, 你是Neil Patrick Harris嗎?
Yep.
對啊.
- Oh, my God, what are you doing here? - Holy shit.
- 哦，天哪，你在這幹嘛? - 太棒了.
Dude, Doogie Howser M.D. was, like, my favorite show growing up.
Doogie Howser M.D.是我 小時侯最喜歡的節目了
You were my idol.
你就是我的偶像.
That's great. Could we get going? l'm bored as shit back here.
那太好了，我們可以走了麼？ 這地方噁心死我了
- Go, go. - Let's go. This is a frickin' boring spot.
- 走，走. - 出發！這地方簡直糟透了
So l gotta ask you, Neil,
問你個問題, Neil,
did you ever get it on with Wanda off the set?
你私底下“搞”過Wanda沒?
Dude, l humped every piece of ass ever on that show.
我上過參與那個節目的所有的人
Even the chick who played the hot nurse?
連那個扮演護士的都......?
No. l didn't go all the way with her.
沒. 我跟她不是一路.
Neil, you wouldn't happen to know
Neil, 你知不知道
how to get on the highway from here, would you?
從這兒怎麼上到高速公路上去?
Dude, l don't even know where the fuck l am right now.
我連現在自己在哪兒都不知道
l was at this party earlier tonight
今晚早些時候我參加了個聚會
and some guy hooked me up with this incredible X.
有個人用個難以置信的東西把 我迷倒了.
The next thing l know, l'm being thrown out of a moving car.
接下來，我就只知道自己被人從 車上扔下來了.
- l've been tripping balls ever since. - That's crazy, dude.
- 我一直在到處遊蕩 - 那太瘋狂了, 哥們.
We've been having a pretty crazy night, too.
我們今天晚上也很瘋狂
We've just been driving around looking for White Castle,
我們一直在開著車找白色城堡,
but we keep getting sidetracked.
但是總是找不到目標
Yeah, dude, you fascinate me.
是啊,老兄,你讓我著迷
Forget White Castle. Let's go get some pussy.
忘了白色城堡 讓我們去找一些姑娘
- Huh? - lt's a fuckin' sausage-fest in here.
- 嗯? - 這埵酗@根饑餓的香腸呢
Let's get us some poontang. Then we'll go to White Castle.
我們找點樂子 再去白色城堡
No, Neil, you don't understand.
不, Neil, 你不懂.
We've been craving these burgers all night.
我們渴望了一晚上的漢堡
Yeah, l've been craving burgers, too--fur burgers.
是啊,我也渴望漢堡---陰毛漢堡
Come on, dudes, let's pick up some trim at a strip club.
來吧,哥們,去脫衣舞俱樂部找點樂子
The Doogie line always works on strippers.
The Doogie line 那兒有許多脫衣舞者
Lap dance.
裸體跳舞
There's a gas station. l'm gonna see if we can get directions.
那有個加油站，去看看 能不能問到路.
We don't need...
我們不用...
Hurry up, dudes, hurry up. l'm losing wood.
快啊, 哥們, 快點. 我是失敗的木頭
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
快，快，快
- Chill. - We'll be right back, Neil.
- 安靜 - 我們會回來的, Neil.
We'll be back.
我們會回來的.
What's the deal with Neil Patrick Harris? Why is he so horny?
Neil Patrick Harris怎麼了? 為什麼這麼著急?
l don't know, but we can't let him interfere with our quest.
我不知道，但是我們不能讓他 耽誤我們的事.
- Oh, God. - Shit, these punks again.
- 哦，暈 - 靠，又是這群龐克男.
Late-night Math League meeting, homos?
又見面了,同志們?
Extreme!
走吧!
Let's go.
我們走
No, no. Pies, pies--no.
不,不 太亂了,太亂了---不要
Dude, what is that? ls that a pterodactyl?
那是什麼玩意？是翼龍嗎？
l do not know what that is.
我不知道.
That was extreme, dude!
太刺激了,老兄!
Excuse me, can you tell us how to get to the highway from here?
打擾了，問一下從這堳蝏簳咫~能上 高速公路?
Dude, l got this.
哥們，看這個.
Dude, who knew learning Hindi would actually pay off?
老兄,誰知道學了印度語會派上用場?
Guy says the highway is, like, a couple traffic lights from here.
那傢伙說公路就離這幾個路燈遠
We should be in Cherry Hill in ten minutes.
我們十分鐘就能到希爾鎮
- Ready? One, two, three! - No. No.
- 預備? 1，2，3! - 不，不.
- No. - Extreme kayaking!
- 不. - 極限獨木舟!
No!
不!
Extreme!
刺激!
- No! - Man, that was so fuckin' extreme!
- 不! - 太刺激了!
On a scale of 1 to 10,
從1到10評分,
one being not so extreme and ten being extremely extreme,
1 是無極限 10是極限中極限,
l give this a 9.5!
我給這個評分9.5!
- Check it out! - Extreme cheddar!
- 看啊! - 刺激的乳酪!
- Hey. - Extreme cashier!
- 嗨 - 刺激的出納員!
Somebody should do something.
得有人做些什麼了.
Yeah, you're right.
是的, 說的對
Hey, asshole! Why don't you leave that guy alone
嘿, 混蛋們! 為什麼不能放這個人一馬？
and go jerk off to some snowboarding videos or something?
別再做那些古怪的行為舉止?
l didn't mean you should do something about it.
我沒說是要你這樣
What? You're gonna take that?
什麼? 你要管?
What's up with that? Huh?
那該怎麼辦?嗯?
You're gonna take that?
你要管嗎?
- Yeah!
- 耶!
- Shit! - That's right, bitch!
- 幹! - 這就對了，白癡!
You just try fuckin' with me one more time!
你試著再幹我一次!
Just try it! Thank you, come again.
再來啊! 歡迎下次光臨
- Yeah!
- 耶!
Kumar, you okay?
卡瑪, 你沒事吧?
Yeah, dude, l just hate those assholes.
沒事, 我就是討厭那幫混蛋.
You know what? Fuck it, l'm hungry. Let's just get outta here.
要我說，去他的，我餓了. 咱們趕緊走吧
Did Doogie Howser just steal my fucking car?
你看到誰偷了我的車嗎?
Yes. l think he did.
是，好象是的
You! You had to pick up a hitchhiker! Why?!
你!都是你非要讓他搭車。 咋辦!?
Calm down.
冷靜一下
Why did you leave the keys in the car?
你為什麼把車鑰匙留在車?
Why? Because it would get stolen.
為什麼? 就是為了讓它被偷唄
l figured that Neil Patrick Harris was a trustworthy guy.
我原以為Neil Patrick Harris這 人可以相信呢
Come on. How was l supposed to know he'd fuck us over?
拜託，我怎麼知道他會做 這種事?
This whole freaking night, this whole night, is your fault!
整個晚上全是怪事, 今天整個晚上,全是你的錯!
- Where are you going? - l'm going inside to call the police.
- 你去哪? - 去店堨晶q話報警.
l don't want to talk to you anymore.
我不想再跟你說話了
- Yeah!
- 耶!
There's a pay phone across the street
街對面有個電話亭，你可以去那打
if you don't wanna deal with those assholes.
如果你不想再碰那撥混蛋
After we talk to the cops, we're still going to White Castle, right?
我們報警之後，就去白色城堡，對吧?
l'm not speaking to you.
我不跟你講話
When are they fucking going to develop button technology
什麼時候他們能發明出那種
that will understand urgency?!
能夠明白緊急情況的按鈕技術?!
- Dude, this is ridiculous. Just walk across. - lt'll change in a second.
- 老兄,太可笑了,走過去吧 - 馬上就會變的
There's not a car in sight. Just go ahead.
四周看不見車. 過去吧
Fine. You want me to cross? l will cross.
好啊. 你要讓我過去? 好啊，我過.
lf it makes you happy,
如果能讓你高興，我這就過.
l'll do it.
我要過了.
Shit!
幹!
- What-- - Sorry.
- 什麼事-- - 對不起.
ls there a problem, Officer Palumbo?
有什麼事情嗎, Palumbo警官?
ls there a problem? You ever heard of jaywalking?
有什麼事情? 你聽說過走路不遵守交通規則嗎?
Yes, l have. l'm really sorry. Won't happen again.
是的,我真的抱歉 不會再發生了
That's great. l'm writing you up a ticket.
那就好了. 我給你開張罰單
A ticket? Are you serious?
罰單? 你說真的?
Who the fuck are you, shitwad?
你是哪個, 狗屎?
Let me apologize for my friend here. l'm very sorry.
讓我替我的朋友道歉 我非常抱歉
l'm really glad you're here. We've had a rough night.
很高興你在這 我們有一個糟糕的晚上
You know the show Doogie Howser M.D. ?
你知道Doogie Howser M.D.秀嗎?
Great show. God, l love that show. ''Doogie.''
不錯的秀 上帝,我喜歡那個秀''Doogie.''
Neil Patrick Harris stole my car tonight.
Neil Patrick Harris 今晚偷了我的車
Hey, NPH wouldn't do that, all right?
嘿, NPH不會那樣做的,是嗎?
Give me some l.D.
給我你們的身份證明
Excuse me, how can you give him a ticket for jaywalking?
不好意思,你怎麼能對走路沒遵守交通 規則的人開罰單?
lt's 2:30 in the morning. There's not a car around here.
現在是早上2:30 這附近沒有車
Kumar, shut up.
卡瑪,閉嘴
That's not the kind of tone you want to use
你不應該用這種語調
on a cop who can bust your ass.
對一個能操翻你屁股的警官說話
- Bust my ass? - Yeah, Koo-mar.
- 操翻我屁股? - 是啊,卡--瑪
Bust your ass.
操翻你屁股
What kind of name is that anyhow? Koo-mar.
什麼垃圾名字?卡--瑪
What is that, like, five O's or two U's?
什麼東西,是有5個o還是2個u?
No, it's actually one U.
不,實際上只有一個u
Yeah, bullshit.
胡說
Whatever happened to good old American names like Dave or Jim?
為什麼不取些好的美國名字 像"DAVE"或者"JIM"
- Harold.
- 哈樂德
- Are you kidd-- - Now that's a great name.
- 你在開玩笑-- - 這個名字不錯
- Let me take care of this. - You should be proud of that name, son.
- 這件事讓我自己來 - 你會因這個名字而驕傲的,孩子
As you were, ladies.
像你們這樣,小姐們
- $220?! Are you crazy?! - Kumar, if you don't stop--
- $220?! 你瘋了嗎?! - 卡瑪,如果你不停下--
No, l understand exactly what's going on here.
不,我知道現在在發生些什麼
Excuse me, officer, let me take a couple of guesses.
對不起,長官,讓我猜想一下
- l'm really sorry-- - Get your hands down!
- 真的抱歉-- - 把你的手放下!
- Okay, alright. - No sudden moves. Back it up!
- 好的,不錯 - 別亂動,放在身後!
You were probably the big asshole in your high school, right?
你在中學時肯定是個大混球, 是嗎?
Absolutely right.
完全正確
Used to pick on guys like us every day, right?
只會抓些像我們這樣的傢伙,對嗎?
With pleasure.
非常樂意
Then graduation day came, and we went to college,
然後畢業的日子到了, 我們上了大學
and you went nowhere, and you thought,
你無處可去, 然後你想
''Hey, how can l still give them shit?
嘿,我怎樣還能捉弄他們?
l know, l'll become a cop.''
我知道了,我應該成為一名警官
Well, congratu-fuckin'-lations. Your dream has come true.
好的,祝賀你 你美夢成真
Now, why don't you just take this quiet little Asian guy
為什麼你只抓這個安靜矮小
with the Anglicized name that treats you so well
有英國化名字的,對你這麼好的亞洲人
and give him a couple of other tickets?
還給他這麼重的罰單?
- Better yet, just take him to jail. - Better idea.
- 把他帶到監獄不是更好嗎 - 更好的主意
Why don't you just arrest him? Does that work out for you okay, Harold?
為什麼不逮捕他? 那對你有用嗎,哈樂德?
- ''Great American name, Harold.'' - Let's go, Harold.
- ''偉大的美國名字,哈樂德'' - 我們走吧,哈樂德
Thanks to your buddy, we're going downtow--
由於你的夥伴, 我們要走一趟--
Oh, shit.
噢,操
Well, thank you so much for being understanding about Bradley.
好的,非常感謝你能理解Bradley.
l promise you he won't ever do it again.
我向你保證他不會再犯了
l'm sure he won't.
我確信他不會
Right, Brad?
對嗎, Brad?
Yes, sir, Officer Palumbo, sir.
是的,先生 Palumbo警官,先生
- Mommy, can we go home? - Get in the car, Bradley Thomas.
- 媽咪,我們能回家嗎? - 上車, Bradley Thomas
Bye, Brad.
再見, Brad
Are you gonna do something about my car?
你要為我的車做什麼嗎?
First our top story.
首先我們的頭條
The search for the escaped cheetah cortirues toright.
今晚對逃跑的印度豹的找尋工作
ht was last spotted ir Rardolph Courty. south of....
最終在羅納多城找到, 南方....
- So what are you in here for? - For being black.
- 你為什麼在這? - 因為是黑人
Seriously.
認真點
l am serious. You wanna know what happened?
我是認真的 你想知道發生什麼嗎?
l was walking out of a Barnes & Noble,
我在Barnes & Noble外面散步
and a cop stops me.
然後一位警官讓我停下
Evidently a black guy robbed a store in Newark.
明顯的一個黑人搶劫了Newark的銀行
l told him, ''l haven't even been to Newark in months.''
我告訴他, ''我幾個月沒去Newark了''
So, he starts beating me with his gun...
然後,他用警棍不停的打我...
- ...telling me to stop resisting arrest. - Holy shit! What'd you do?
- ...告訴我停止反抗 - 操他媽的! 你怎麼做?
l kept saying, ''l understand l'm under arrest.
我不停的說, ''我知道我被捕了
Now please stop beating me.''
現在別打我了''
l don't understand how you can be so calm about all this.
我不明白為什麼你對這一切如此冷靜
Look at me. l'm fat, black, can't dance,
看我 我肥,黑,不會跳舞
and l have two gay fathers.
還有兩個同性戀父親
People have been messing with me my whole life.
人們把我的一生都搞的混亂
l learned a long time ago that there's no sense getting all riled up
很久之前我學會了不要對每件事動怒
every time a bunch of idiots give you a hard time.
不要在意每次一群傻瓜對你的為難
ln the end, the universe tends to unfold as it should.
最後,事情總會好起來的
Plus l have a really large penis. That keeps me happy.
加上我有一個真正的大屌 那讓我很高興
Hey, hey, listen up, guys!
嘿,嘿,聽著,夥計
Multiple gunshots fired in Millbrook Park.
Millbrook Park有槍戰發生
Finally, some action. l'm goin'!
要採取行動了 我去!
- No, l'm goin'! - Lock and load!
- 不,我去! - 鎖上,帶裝備
That was strange.
真奇怪
What the hell was that?
那到底是些什麼?
Rold. ls that you?
羅德,是你嗎?
- Kumar? - Are the cops still here?
- 卡瑪? - 警官們還在嗎?
What the hell are you doing?
你究竟在幹什麼?
l just called and made up some story about a shooting in Millbrook Park.
我只打了個電話, 騙他們說Millbrook Park有槍戰
- Jesus Christ, what'd you do that for? - l'm fucking starving.
- 上帝,你幹嘛那樣做? - 我他媽的餓死了
l figured l'd bust you out and we'd go get some burgers.
我會救你出去,然後我們去吃漢堡
Forget it. l'm not getting into any more trouble.
別提了,我不想再惹什麼麻煩
l'm already in here because of you.
我因為你才來這堛
Hey, fuck you!
嘿,操你!
What did you want me to do, stand there and take the hit?
你要我做些什麼, 站在那兒接受教訓?
You know l've never taken a swing at you, ever.
你知道我從沒有求過你
Well, l never got your car stolen.
我從沒把你的車弄丟
- Fine. l'm leaving. - Fine.
- 好的,我走了 - 好的
- Harold, how do l get out of here? - How the hell should l know?
- 哈樂德,我怎麼從這兒出去? - 我怎麼會知道?
Shit! Oh, God, this isn't good.
操! 噢,天啊,情況不妙
My ass!
我的屁股!
Sure you don't want to get out of here?
真的不想離開這嗎?
And become a fugitive? Are you nuts?
成為一個逃亡者? 你是白癡嗎?
- The guy has all my information. - So what?
- 那傢伙有我所有的資料 - 那又怎樣?
We'll just take what he wrote down about you and leave.
我們把那些資料帶走就行了
Unless you want to stay here all night
除非你想整夜呆在這
and not be able to turn in your work tomorrow.
明天也不回去工作了
Fine, hurry up.
好的,快點
Yes! All right, we gotta find keys.
是!好的,我們必須找到鑰匙
Oh, yes!
噢!在這
Sweet! l was hoping it would be one of these big ring of keys.
妙極了! 希望就在這大串鑰匙堶
- Kumar, hurry the fuck up. - All right, yeah.
- 卡瑪,你動作快點 -  好的,耶
- Yes! - Dude!
- 搞定! - 哥們!
- Hey, what's that smell? - What smell?
- 嘿,什麼氣味? - 什麼氣味?
Kumar.
卡瑪
hf we still have time. we might still get by
如果我們仍然有時間 我們會依舊在一起
Every time h thirk about it h warra cry
每當我想起你 我就會哭泣
With bombs ard the devil. ard the kids keep comir'
和炸彈與魔鬼 還有孩子們一起
No way to breathe easy. ro time to be yourg
沒辦法呼吸暢快 沒時間年輕
But h tell myself that h'm doir' all right
但是我告訴我自己 我會整晚的幹
There's rothir' left to do at right
沒有留下任何一點
But go crazy or you
為你瘋狂
Let me go crazy. crazy or you
讓我瘋狂
Bitch! Learn how to fuckin' make coffee, you fuckin' whore!
賤人!學著怎麼煮咖啡,你都搞雜了!
Let me go crazy. crazy or you
為你瘋狂
l love you.
我愛你
No, no, no.
不,不,不
No, baby, come on.
不,寶貝,來吧
Hey, Kumar. Kumar! Where are you--
嘿,卡瑪,卡瑪! 你去哪兒--
Kumar! Still in jail, asshole!
卡瑪! 還在監獄呢,混蛋!
Come here!
過來!
Kumar! The cops--
卡瑪!警官--
You thought you'd get away with it, huh?
你認為你逃脫了嗎,嗯?
l was in bed. l didn't fire any gun. l swear.
我在床上 我沒有放任何槍,我發誓
Hey, Jackson's trying to escape!
嘿, Jackson想要逃跑!
What are you talking about? l'm just sitting here.
你在說什麼呢? 我就坐在這
He's trying to break free! Get him!
他想要逃跑! 抓住他!
- Aw, shit. - Don't move!
- 噢,操 - 別動!
Stop resisting! We need backup now!
停止反抗! 我們需要後援!
- He's got a gun. - That's not a gun, that's a book.
- 他有一支槍 - 那不是槍,是本書
- Secure the book! - Book is secure.
- 檢查那本書! - 書是安全的
You bring this filth in here? What is this shit?
你把這種東西帶來的? 什麼鬼東西?
Wait, wait. We gotta do something about this.
等下,等下, 我們要做點什麼
We're gonna teach you how to read now, brother.
我們要教你怎麼讀書,兄弟
lf l were you, l'd leave as soon as possible.
如果我是你,我會儘快離開
- Whose hand is that? - Thanks, man.
- 那是誰的手? - 謝謝
Jesus Christ. Thanks for getting me out, man.
上帝 謝謝你把我救出來
No problem. The burgers wouldn't taste as good if you weren't there.
沒問題,沒你在的話漢堡也吃的不香
Hey, look at this.
嘿,看這個
lt's like we went from being completely poor to being millionaires.
好像我們從一窮二白突然變成百萬富翁
- What was that? - Probably just a coyote.
- 那是什麼? - 或許只是山狗
Aren't people supposed to be scared of coyotes?
人們不是應該害怕山狗嗎?
That's just 'cause they sound scary, man.
那只是因為他們叫起來很可怕,兄弟
ln one-on-one combat, either of us could take down a coyote, no problem.
一對一的戰鬥,我們兩個中任何一個 都能對付一個山狗
What?
什麼?
Now, cheetahs are another story.
印度豹就不一樣了
- We're gonna die. - No, now hold on.
- 我們會死的 - 不會,冷靜點
Cheetahs are used to eating gazelles and shit.
印度豹習慣吃羚羊和狗屎
They're not known for eating humans.
他們不知道吃人
That is a corpse. We're gonna die.
那是一個屍體 我們要死了
Shit! That's not a good sign.
操! 不是一個好跡象
Maybe if we just stay really, really still, he'll just go away.
也許我們安靜的呆著,安靜的呆著 它就會走開的
Okay.
好的
Just stay really still. Don't move, okay?
真正的呆著 別動,好嗎?
Just stay right there. Very good. Good job.
就呆在那兒 非常好,幹的不錯
This isn't working.
沒有用
He's mauling me!
它在咬我!
Dude, l told you not to bring the beef jerky.
老兄,我告訴過你別拿牛肉幹
He likes me.
它喜歡我
Hey, Rold, l have an idea.
嘿,羅德,我有個主意
- You gotta be kidding me, man. - Uh-uh.
- 你一定是在耍我,老兄 - 啊哈
This is either a really smart move
這真是一個明智的舉動
or by far the stupidest thing that we have ever tried.
或者是我們目前為止做的最蠢的事情
Well, we're about to find out.
好的,我們將要發現
Mush!
走!
l told you this was--
我告訴過你這是--
Oy vey!
噢!
Dude, am l really high, or is this actually working?
老兄,真的很爽 竟然成功了!
- Both! - This is awesome!
- 一樣! - 太驚人了!
We're gonna be at White Castle in no time!
我們馬上就會到白色城堡!
That was close, huh, Roldy?
就在眼前,哈,羅德
Harold. l need you, Harold.
哈樂德 我需要你,哈樂德
Come here.
過來
- Come here, Harold. - Maria.
- 過來,哈樂德 - 瑪利亞
- Come, Harold. - l'm coming, baby!
- 來,哈樂德 - 我來了,寶貝!
l want you to hold me. Papi. l need you.
我要你抱住我 親愛的,我需要你
Baby, l'm a-comin'!
寶貝,我來了!
Not so fast.
沒這麼快
w atch out, watch out
當心,當心
Come on!
來吧!
Bullets--my only weakness. How did you know?
子彈--我唯一的弱點 你怎麼知道?
Maria
瑪利亞
Harold.
哈樂德
Maria. Maria
瑪利亞,瑪利亞
w atch out, watch out
當心,當心
What the hell are you doing? God!
天啊,你他媽的在幹什麼?
You've been out cold for the past half-hour.
你昏了半個小時了
l figured maybe if l did some gay shit you'd wake up.
我估計做一些同志舉動 會讓你醒過來
lf we did some gay shit? Where are we?
為什麼做那個? 我們在哪兒?
Didn't we come here on a cheetah? Where's the cheetah?
我們是坐印度豹來到這堛熄? 印度豹去哪兒了?
lt ran away. Listen, forget about the cheetah, okay?
它跑了,聽著,忘了那頭豹子,好嗎?
l have some bad news and some worse news.
我有一些壞消息,和更壞的消息
Give me the worse news first.
先告訴我更壞的消息
l looked at some of the road signs up there,
我在那邊看到一些路標
and it looks like the cheetah took us in the wrong direction.
看起來好像印度豹把我們帶到了 相反的方向
- Shit! - Yeah.
- 操! - 是的
All right, what's the bad news?
好吧, 那壞消息是什麼?
Your laptop's completely destroyed.
你的筆記本電腦完全摔碎了
What?
什麼?
Why didn't-- Why didn't you tell me--
為什麼不-- 為什麼你不告訴我--
How is that not the worse news?
為什麼這個不是更壞的消息?
The laptop situation really only affects you,
電腦的事情只影響了你
whereas the White Castle situation affects both of us equally.
白色城堡的事的確影響了我們兩個人
Oh, no! Oh, no!
噢,不!噢,不!
All my work was saved on this computer.
我所有的工作都保存在電腦!
Now l gotta go back to the office and redo it.
現在我必須返回辦公室重新做了
Exactly. First we'll go to White Castle--
正確的是, 首先我們去白色城堡--
Forget about White Castle. There is no time.
別提白色城堡 沒時間了
Car.
車
Hello. Over here!
你好
Shit.
操
Whoa.
喔
Yeah. Um...
耶,嗯...
All right, we'll get a pay phone,
好吧, 我們需要公用電話
get a cab back to your office, all right?
叫輛計程車帶你回辦公室,好嗎?
Come on. You all right?
來吧,你還好嗎?
- Hey, check this out! - Yeah, nice!
- 嘿,看啊! - 耶,不錯!
Hey, Apu!
嗨,Apu!
Jesus. These guys are frickin' everywhere.
老天,這些傢伙哪兒都在
Who's looking after the Kwik-E-Mart while you're gone?
你們走了，誰來照看Kwik-E-Mart？
You two going to share a curry Slurpee?
你們兩個要來爽一下嗎?
Fucking assholes.
混蛋
Dude, check it out. lt's Rosenberg and Goldstein.
老兄,看啊 是羅森柏格和金斯坦
l want that.
我要那個
What, a Hot Dog Heaven super chili cheese dog?
什麼,一個熱狗天堂的 超級紅椒乾酪熱狗?
No. l want that feeling.
不,我要那種感覺
The feeling that comes over a man
那種男人能感受到的
when he gets exactly what he desires.
真正得到滿足的感覺
l need that feeling.
我需要那種感覺
Are you saying what l think you're saying?
你在說我想讓你說的嗎?
- We gotta go to White Castle. - Yes, yes!
- 我們必須去白色城堡 - 是的,是的!
l knew you had it in you, dude.
老兄,我知道你是這麼想的
Yo, is that Cindy Kim?
唷,那是金辛蒂嗎?
Oh, dude, you should've boned her when you had the chance, man.
噢,老兄,幸虧你有機會時沒有去上她
Check it out.
看著
Why don't you guys just leave us alone?
為什麼你們這些傢伙只針對我們
What are you gonna do about it, Mr. Miyagi?
你想要怎樣, Miyagi先生?
That's extreme, man!
太刺激了,夥計!
There's ro serse gettirg all riled up
不要對每件事動怒
every time a burch of idiots give you a hard time.
不要在意每次一群傻瓜對你的為難
The uriverse terds to urfold as it should.
最後,事情總會好起來的
Nothing.
沒什麼
- Fucking extreme! - l'm so sick of their bullshit.
- 太刺激了! - 看他們胡說真的很噁心
Don't worry. The universe tends to unfold as it should.
別擔心, 最後,事情總會好起來的
What is that, some fortune cookie?
那是什麼, 一些幸運小甜餅?
Hey, l got a plan. Follow my lead, okay?
嘿,我有一個計畫 跟我幹,好嗎
- Your lead? - Yeah.
- 跟你幹? - 是的
Okay.
好的
Whoa, what are you doing? Oh, shit!
喔, 你在幹什麼? 噢,操!
Those pricks!
那些屌人!
- This is your plan? - lt's working, isn't it?
- 這是你的計畫? - 成功了,不是嗎?
Come on, come on! Get 'em, guys!
快點,快點! 抓住他們,兄弟們!
- Jerk-offs! - My truck!
- 他們跑了! - 我的卡車!
Thank you, come again.
歡迎下次光臨
Dude, that was so not extreme.
老兄,這一點也不刺激
l know, Extreme Sport Punk Number One.
我知道, 極限運動第一龐克
l know.
我知道
Let's find us some tunes, baby.
找點音樂來聽吧,寶貝
''Cole's Extreme Mix, Volume 5''? What is this shit?
''科爾的刺激混音, 第五卷''? 這是什麼垃圾?
Ard h reed you row toright
今晚我需要你
Those guys are fuckin' posers.
那些傢伙真是一群裝腔作勢的人
Ard if you'll orly hold me tight
只要你緊緊抓住我
Baby. baby. the stars are shirirg foryou
寶貝,寶貝,星星為你閃耀
Ard just like me. h'm sure that they adore you
就像我一樣 我確信他們也愛慕你
Baby. baby
寶貝,寶貝
Go walkirg through the forest
穿過森林
Thirgs'll go your way
一切如你所願
Someday somebody's gonna make you wanna turn around
有一天有人會讓你回頭
- And say good-bye - Say good-bye
- 然後說再見 - 說再見
Until then, baby
直到永遠,寶貝
Are you gonna let 'em hold you down and make you cry?
你要他們讓你哭泣?
Don't you know things can change
你不知道事情已經改變
Things'll go your way
一切如你所願
lf you hold on for one more day
只要你把握今天
Hold on
把握
Bingo.
逮住了
Yeah, dude! Cherry Hill, man. We're almost there.
耶,老兄!徹塈ざ蜃 我們快到了
l told you, man!
我告訴你了,夥計
l found 'em, and l'm gonna need backup.
我找到他們了, 我需要後援
- Oh, shit. - Shit.
- 噢,操 - 操
Fudge, dude. Are you kidding me?
操你,老兄 你在玩我嗎?
- What the hell are you doing? - l'm not going back to jail, man.
- 你他媽的在幹什麼? - 我不想回到監獄,夥計
We've come too far. Now buckle up. Buckle up!
我們已經走這麼遠了 現在扣緊,扣緊!
We got a chase on our hands.
我在跟著他們
- Ready? - Yeah. For what?
- 準備好了? - 好了,要幹嘛?
Oh, shit!
噢,操!
- Where the fuck you takin' us? - Just hold on.
- 你要把我們帶到哪兒去? - 抓緊
What the...
哪兒去了...
lt's a good thing l have an empty stomach or else l'd puke right now.
幸好我是空著肚子的, 要不然都得吐出來
We're gonna make it.
我們要成功了
Everything's gonna be all ri--
每件事都會好起--
Oh, my God!
噢,天啊!
Oh, shit. Holy shit.
噢,操!操他媽的
- Put her in reverse. Hurry! - Shit!
- 倒回去,快點! - 操!
Let's go out the back. l'll go first.
我們從後面出去 我先
- Don't shake the car! - Well, hurry up!
- 別搖動車 - 好的,快點!
Hey, Roldy, check it out.
嘿,羅德,看啊
Shit, shit! We're trapped, man!
操,操! 我們被困住了,夥計!
Whoa. Not necessarily.
喔,不一定
No.
不
No, not a chance. l'd rather turn myself in than die.
不,沒有機會了 我還不如進去然後死掉
No, dude, l know exactly how to do that.
不,老兄,我清楚該怎麼做
l used to do it with my dad all the time when l was a kid.
小時候我經常和爸爸一起幹那些事情
Forget it! l'm not risking my life over a bunch of hamburgers, man.
別提了!我不會為了幾個漢堡而 冒生命危險,夥計
So you think this is just about the burgers, huh?
所以你認為這只是為了漢堡嗎,嗯?
Let me tell you, it's about far more than that.
讓我告訴你, 遠比漢堡要多
Our parents came to this country,
我們的父母來到這個國家,
escaping persecution, poverty, and hunger.
逃離迫害, 貧窮,和饑餓
Hunger, Harold.
饑餓,哈樂德
They were very, very hungry.
他們非常非常的餓
They wanted to live in a land that treated them as equals,
他們想居住在一塊平等對待他們 的土地上
a land filled with hamburger stands.
一塊站滿了漢堡的土地
And not just one type of hamburger, okay?
不只是一種漢堡,對嗎?
Hundreds of types with different sizes, toppings, and condiments.
幾百種不同種類,大小,味道的漢堡
That land was America.
那塊熱土就是美國
America, Harold! America!
美國,哈樂德!美國!
Now, this is about achieving what our parents set out for.
現在,我們是要完成父母交給我們的任務
This is about the pursuit of happiness.
這關係著我們的幸福
This night... is about the American dream.
這個晚上... 是關於那個美國夢的
Dude, we can stay here, get arrested,
老兄,我們可以呆在這 等待被捕
and end our hopes of ever going to White Castle.
永遠結束我們去白色城堡的夢想
Or we can take that hang glider and make our leap towards freedom.
或者我們乘著那架滑翔機 朝自由飛去
l leave the decision up to you.
我把選擇權交給你
l hate you, Kumar.
我恨你,卡瑪
Tilt forward.
傾斜好方向
- Roldy. - What?
- 羅德 - 什麼?
- Don't worry. Everything's gonna be fine. - All right.
- 別擔心,所有事情都會好起來的 - 好的
- Good job, Rold. Keep running. - Thank you.
- 幹得好,羅德,繼續跑 - 謝謝
Hey, Roldy, there's something l forgot to tell you.
嘿,羅德,有些事情要告訴你
- l've never hang-glided before. - What?!
- 我以前從沒玩過滑翔機 - 什麼?!
Jump!
跳!
Oh, my God!
噢,我的天!
- Dude, it's working! - Oh, my God!
- 老兄,成功了! - 噢,我的天!
Yeah!
耶!
Good news.
好消息
l just found enough dope in the car
我在車塈鋮鴗F足夠的大麻
to put these skateboard punks in jail for the next couple of years.
讓這些滑冰朋克男蹲幾年監獄了
- Dude, we're so high right now. - We're not low.
- 老兄,我們現在太爽了 - 是啊
All right, l'm bringing her in. Right, left, left.
好的,我們到白色城堡那去吧 右,左,左
Perfect!
完美!
- Shit!
- 操!
God!
上帝
l'm gonna kill you!
我要殺了你!
Look!
看!
We made it, dude.
我們成功了,老兄
Looks like you guys had some night, huh?
看起來你們忙了一夜了,嗯?
l want 30 Slyders, 5 French fries, and 4 large Cherry Cokes.
我要30份漢堡,5份炸薯條, 還有4杯大可樂
l want the same, except make mine Diet Cokes, Chuck.
我要一樣的,給我健怡可樂
Wow. Well, that comes to $46.75.
喔,一共是 $46.75
- Dude, where's my money? - You don't have money?
- 老兄,我的錢去哪兒了? - 你沒帶錢?
- Dude, are you kidding me? - No.
- 哥們,你在開玩笑嗎? - 不
l gave mine to that asshole at Princeton.
我的錢給了普林斯頓的那個混蛋
Fuck! Fuck that hippie fuck! No! Dude, this isn't happening!
操!操死那個嬉皮士 不!不能這樣
We didn't make it here, and now we're broke!
現在我們一分錢都沒有了
No, no, no, no!
不,不,不,不!
Guys, let me pay for it. lt's the least l can do.
夥計,讓我幫你們付帳吧 這是我僅能做的了
The hell are you doing here?
你他媽的在這堸竣偵?
You guys kept talking about White Castle last night so much,
你們昨晚談論白色城堡那麼爽,
it made me start to crave it, too.
也讓我對它燃起了渴望
- Dude, where's my car? - Where's his car, dude?
- 老兄,我的車在哪兒? - 他的車在哪兒,老兄?
Yeah, sorry about that. l told you last night l was tripping balls.
是的,我很抱歉 昨晚我告訴過你們我要去舞會
l don't know what came over me.
不知道是什麼抓住了我
Your car's in the parking lot. Here are your keys.
你的車在停車場 給你鑰匙
Do you realize what the hell we had to go through after you took the car?
你意識到在你開走車之後 我們經歷了些多少苦難嗎
Yeah. lt was a dick move on my part.
是的,我做了個愚蠢的舉動
That's why l'm paying for your meal. Prick.
那就是我為什麼要幫你們付帳,屌人
Thanks, l guess.
謝謝,或許
Here's 50 bucks for the burgers and 200 for the car.
這是漢堡的50美元, 還有200美元賠你們的車
What happened to my car?
我的車怎麼了?
l made some love stains in the back seat.
我在後座上留下了一些愛的瑕疵
You'll see.
你會看到的
Anyway, nice meeting you guys. l'll catch you later.
不管怎樣,很高興碰到你們 一會見
Where are you going?
你去哪兒?
Wherever God takes me.
天知道
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
喔,喔,喔
Let's do this together.
讓我們一起來
Damn, that hit the spot.
媽的,真是恰到好處
- That was the best meal of my life. - Mine, too.
- 這是我一生中吃過最好的食物了 - 我也是
You know what, dude?
老兄,你知道嗎
l think l may actually go to my interview today.
我想我應該會去今天的面試
Are you serious?
你在認真的說嗎?
You know, my whole life l've just been scared
你知道我一生中最害怕的就是
of being one of those nerdy lndian guys turned doctor,
成為那些卑微的 印度人醫生中的一員
but tonight got me thinking.
但是今晚讓我想通了
There are far worse things in this world than being tapped
這個世界上還有更糟的事情
for having a natural ability in medicine.
比上醫學院更糟糕
Plus, how cool was that, saving that dude's life last night?
加上,那又是絕妙的 昨晚挽救了那個傢伙的生命?
lt was somewhere between that, getting yelled at by my dad,
通過那些事情 被我老爸教訓
and seeing Neil Patrick Harris
遇到Neil Patrick Harris
that l realized that l've always wanted to be a doctor
我意識到, 我確實想成為一個醫生
but l've just been too scared to admit it to myself.
我只是害怕接納我自己
- Billy, you paying for this? - Yeah, l'll be there--
- 比利,你付帳? - 是的,我來--
Good, 'cause if he wasn't, you would.
好的, 因為如果他不付 就由你來
Are you listening to me, Roldy? l'm having a major epiphany here.
你在聽我說嗎,羅德? 我在談重要的事情
l'll be right back.
我一會回來
You're unlike any other woman l've ever met.
你跟我見過的其他女人都不一樣
What the fuck is going on here?
這埵b進行些什麼?
Harold? What happened to you, man?
哈樂德? 你怎麼了,夥計?
Never mind me. What the fuck are you doing here?
別在意我, 你他媽的在這堸竣偵?
l thought you and J.D. were busy all night with clients.
我以為你和J.D. 與客戶們忙了一整晚
lsn't that why l had to do your work?
那不是我要幫你工作的原因嗎?
- Henry, what the hell's going on? - Back off, cock boy.
- 亨利,你在幹些什麼? - 退後,屌人
What l said to him goes double for you.
我對他說的也是對你說的
- Did you just call me cock boy? - Yeah, you know l did.
- 你叫我屌人? - 是的,你聽到了
You're just stalling
你們只是畜生
because you're not quick enough to think of a comeback.
因為你們的反應太慢了
You think l'm not quick enough. Guy thinks l'm not quick enough.
你覺得我不夠快 那傢伙說我不夠快
Well, l've got news for you. l am quick enough...
好的,我告訴你最新的消息 我會很快...
...cock boy!
...屌人!
Listen, Harold, l'm really sorry.
聽著,哈樂德,我真的抱歉
Don't bother with him. We'll take it up with Berenson tomorrow.
別煩他了 我們明天和貝爾森談談
What are you gonna tell Berenson?
你要告訴貝爾森什麼?
That l'm your workhorse?
告訴他我是你們的馱馬嗎?
That you guys think you can party all weekend,
你們就可以玩一個週末
leave the work to the quiet Asian guy in the office?
把工作留給這個安靜的亞洲人?
- No, you don't understand.
- 不,你不明白
l'm not doing your work for you anymore.
我不會再做你的工作了
And if either one of you douche bags
如果你們哪一個要
ever tries to pull this shit again,
或者試著再提起這件事
l'll go to Berenson myself.
我會自己去跟貝爾森說
l'll tell him what's really going on.
我將告訴他到底發生了些什麼
And l'll tell the whole office
我還會告訴他
how you both caught gonorrhea from that prostitute in Atlantic City.
你們是怎麼從Atlantic City的 妓女那堭o到淋病的
lf you'll excuse me, boys, l gotta get going. Kumar.
如果沒什麼事 我必須得走了,卡瑪
See you boys at the office on Monday.
星期一辦公室見
Excuse me.
不好意思
Dude, that was awesome! Where the hell did that come from?
老兄,你太牛B了! 你他媽的哪兒來的勇氣?
l don't know.
我不知道
Eating those delicious burgers made me feel like a new man.
吃了那些美味的漢堡 讓我感覺像變成了另外一個人
You know what?
你知道嗎?
Now l'm actually looking forward to going to work this week.
現在我真盼望著馬上開始工作
No shit. You know, you might be worthwhile after all.
操,你知道這一切都是值得的
l'm not worthless.
我有自己的價值
Hey, so those dudes really have gonorrhea?
嘿,那些傢伙真的得了淋病嗎?
Beats me.
我也不知道
Hey.
嘿
- Let's get going. - What's the rush, dude?
- 我們回家吧 - 幹嘛這麼趕,老兄
l don't have my interview for a couple of hours.
我還有幾個小時才面試呢
l got some unfinished business to take care of.
我有些沒完成的工作
l thought those guys were gonna do the work.
我想那些傢伙會搞定那些工作的
No, unfinished business.
不,沒完成的事情
- Maria. - Still not following you.
- 瑪利亞 - 還是跟不上你
Get in!
進來!
So you don't even have a plan.
你甚至沒做個計畫?
Dude, l got love on my side, man.
老兄,我擁有愛就行了
Trust me.
相信我
When l see Maria, l'm gonna know exactly what to say.
當我看到瑪利亞, 我會知道 該怎麼說
- Hey.
- 嗨
lt looks like you guys have had some night.
看起來你們像是忙了一夜
Shit. You know what? l left my lighter in your car.
操,鬼知道 我怎麼把打火機落在車上了
Do me a favor and run down and get it for me, please?
去下面等我一下,我們去拿回來
l gotta urinate.
我先小便
You sure got a lot of baggage.
你確實有很多行李
Maria, wait.
瑪利亞,等等
l know this is gonna seem completely out of the blue,
我知道這看起來確實很突然,
and l know you don't know me very well--or, um, at all.
我知道你也不是很瞭解我-- 或者,根本不瞭解
But let me tell you the best part of my day is.
但是讓我告訴你我一天中 最美的時光是哪個部分
l come home from work and l walk through this lobby,
我工作回家 然後走進這個電梯
and on days that l'm lucky enough,
幸運的話
l spend ten seconds in this elevator with you.
我會在這個電梯與你一起呆幾秒鐘
l had the craziest night of my life tonight,
今晚我有一個瘋狂的夜晚
and l guess l learned that if you want something or someone,
或許我學到了一點, 如果你想得到一樣東西
you have to go for it.
你必須去爭取
And if Liane can marry a guy like Freakshow
如果莉安也能嫁給Freakshow
and l can hang-glide and l can ride a cheetah,
如果我也能飛翔 也能騎上印度豹
then l guess...
那麼我想...
Oh, fuck it.
喔,操
Give me a minute. This is crazy.
等下,這太瘋狂了
- That was...l'm sorry. - l don't even know you.
- 那個...對不起 - 我甚至不瞭解你
l had White Castle, so l'm a little dizzy.
我吃了白色城堡的漢堡, 所以有一點眩暈
- We don't ever speak. - We don't talk, so that was inappropriate.
- 我們從沒談過 - 我們沒談過,所以這不合適
Oh, fuck it.
噢,操
h warra get rext to you
我要在你身邊
Okay.
好的
Now you just have to work on your timing.
現在你可以去做你的事情了
- Where are you going? - Amsterdam.
- 你要去哪兒? - Amsterdam
l'll be back in ten days. But l'll see you when l get back?
10天后回來 回來後會去拜訪你
Yeah, let's do that.
好吧,就這樣
Bye, Harold.
拜,哈樂德
Bye. Bye. l'll see you later.
拜,拜 再見
- She touch your penis? - What?
- 她跟你做了嗎? - 什麼?
What happened?
發生什麼了?
Nothing much, really. Just a little kiss action.
沒什麼,真的 只是一些親吻的舉動
Nice. Nice!
棒極了,棒極了!
Yeah. She's going to Amsterdam. She'll be back in ten days.
是的,她要去Amsterdam 10天后回來
We gotta go.
我們得去
- Where? - Amsterdam, man.
- 哪兒? - Amsterdam, 夥計
- We gotta get our bags packed... - Amsterdam?
- 我們得去整理我們的行李... - Amsterdam?
...and frickin' take the next flight out.
...就乘下一班飛機
Are you freaking out of your mind? What about your interview?
你的不會真的這樣想把? 面試怎麼辦?
Dude, whatever. l'll tell my dad to reschedule it.
老兄,不管怎樣 我會告訴老爸重新安排一次
He won't have a problem as long as l take it seriously for a change.
只要我認真對待 他那邊就不成問題
We gotta freakin' go to Europe and find Maria.
我們必須得去歐洲找到瑪利亞
Dude, she's coming back in ten days.
老兄,她10天后就回來
lt's not like l'm never gonna see her again.
我們會再見到的
Listen, for a hot chick,
聽著,對一個熱辣的少女來說
ten days in Europe can be the kiss of death, okay?
在歐洲的10天會被吻到死的,對嗎?
She's gonna have all these suave, sophisticated guys all over her.
會有許多詭異的男人圍繞在她身邊
When she gets back, she may not be available.
當她回來時,已經過期了
Forget it. l'll see her when she comes back.
別說了,我會在她回來後見到她
Hey, Roldy.
嘿,羅德
You do realize what's legal in Amsterdam, don't you?
你還沒意識到在Amsterdam什麼是合法的, 不是嗎?
Oh, yeah.
噢,是的
ln today's headlines, Rutgers professor Tarik Jackson
今天的頭條, Tarik Jackson教授
and attorney Nathaniel Banks are suing the state of New Jersey
和Nathaniel Banks律師 在新澤西州上訴
for racial discrimination and police brutality.
人種歧視和員警暴力
My family and l are outraged
我和我的家庭受到歧視
and will settle for nothing less than justice.
我們只想要公平
l still trust and love all white people, all of them.
我仍然相信和熱愛白人,所有的白人
And Asians.
還有亞洲人 亞洲人
And a few Mexicans as well.
還有一些墨西哥人
Several of the officers suspected of brutality
一些警官涉嫌使用暴力
were taken into custody earlier this morning.
今早已經被拘留
Run away, you mother...
滾開, 你媽的...
No black mother...gonna get away with this, so...all y'all.
黑人他媽的...必須滾開 操...你們所有的
You can suck my...
你來吮我的...
Police in Cherry Hill, New Jersey,
新澤西徹塈ざ蜃磲滬警
have just arrested a gang of hooligans
抓獲了一群小流氓
who are suspected of terrorizing numerous strip malls
涉嫌恐嚇商店
and convenience stores.
還有藏匿毒品
Officer Thurmond Brucks found their abandoned car,
Thurmond Brucks警官 找到了他們拋棄的車
which contained a large bag of marijuana.
堶惘酗@大包大麻
And in other news, the Muckleburg Police Department
其他消息, Muckleburg警署
are still looking for a fugitive
正在尋找一個逃亡者
who escaped from the police station last night
他昨晚從警署逃脫
with a companion believed to be his accomplice.
與他的同伴一起
Police have released sketches of the two fugitives
警方已經發佈了他們的畫像
which they believe to be extremely accurate.
相信很精確
Nice!
妙!